Harvey,I don't need a perp
walk or a front page headline.
I just want the person responsible.
Then hand me the deal we just
negotiated and justice will be served.
You know what,if this
were anyone else but you,
I wouldn't even be giving
the courtesy of this meeting.
Becky,we're both benefiting from
this. You've got nothing on my client.
And I'm gonna help you
get the person responsible.
So why don't we just go do that?
You better make sure miss stone signs
this. Otherwise,we don't have a deal.
- How long have we known each other?
- Since you were in the DA's office.
Then you know we'll have a deal.
****
- How'd it go with the department of justice?
- Follow me,you'll find out.
- I get to sit in?
- With your head down and your mouth shut.
This isn't a usual
What are you doing? Quick. Act like
you're telling me something important.
- I am telling you something important.
- And then after the injunction,
you know,both parties
decided to reassess--
My God. That woman with Rachel, I took
the lsats for her a couple years ago.
If she saw me,she could blow my cover.
Oh,really? And how would that go?
"Excuse me,when I was cheating for my lsats, that
was the guy who took the test for me"? Come on.
It could go down like that. You
don't know. People say things.
Miss stone,correct me if any of this is
wrong, but you and I both know it's not.
Please address me and
not my client,Mr. specter.
You mean your client who purchased
$10 million in Lunardi pharmaceuticals
and then a day later word of their fda approval
got out and the stock shot up to $30 million?
She purchased that stock for your
clients, Burt Kimball and Dean Morello,
based on a tip sheet
handed out by your clients.
An allegation that
tainted their reputation,
yet the DOJ looked into
it and found nothing.
That doesn't mean it didn't happen.
I'll turn your client over
in person,no handcuffs.
It'll be a country club prison.
And I'll make sure she's processed as
gently as possible as long as she admits
that she made this
trade of her own accord.
It's a crappy deal
wrapped in pretty paper.
Why aren't we dealing with
the department of justice?
Because the DOJ wanted to put you behind bars
for seven years,and I got 'em down to 11 months.
Look,it's a great deal.
You're gonna sign it,you're
gonna serve your year in prison,
and every night when you climb into your
bunk, you're gonna thank your lucky stars
that Harvey specter
negotiated on your behalf.
Nobody's ever gonna believe me, and I don't
have the resources to fight this thing forever.
So I'll sign the goddamn deal.
But I'm not thanking anybody.
Harvey,you came through.
My company's reputation means
everything to me. Thank you.
So I trust we won't be hearing from
the department of justice again?
Unless you plan on inviting them to
the company's Christmas party,Bert,no.
- I told Morello you could fix this for us.
- Thank you,Harvey.
Reality's starting to sink in.
Gabby's a little wound up right now.
Let's give her a minute.
I've got the pretty papers in
my office for you to look over.
Keep an eye on her.
- You here to make sure I don't change my mind about the deal?
- No.
Would you?
You know,my father was a teacher.
He worked hard,followed the rules.
Last year,the district cut his
pension to save their budget.
I went to wall street so I could make some
money before getting into teaching myself.
I never thought I'd have to worry
if they let convicted felons teach.
Can I get you some water or something?
I'm just gonna get you some water.
- I got it.
- Thanks.
- So that girl you were with earlier, she a friend of yours?
- Theresa,yeah.
She used to be a paralegal
here. We were pretty close.
She worked at Pearson,hardman?
And I just had the unique pleasure of giving her
the summer intern tour for prospective employees.
- Really?
- Yeah.
She's in her second year of Harvard law,
meeting with the partners as we speak.
I know. We used to do
everything together.
And now,if she gets this job,she
will technically be my boss.
Oh,God. I'm so sorry,Rachel.
Do you need to talk about it?
No. Not now. Thanks.
- Oh,no,no. No.
- What?
She's gone.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=
-Sync:海带怎么还没白回来
Suits S01E06
You left her alone to get her a water?
- What,she didn't want a latte?
- I was trying to be helpful.
You were very helpful to her.
You didn't see her,Harvey. She
was scared. She was a wreck.
Maybe that had to do with the fact that
she was about to go to prison for 11 months.
I think she was having the
reaction of an innocent woman.
And what was telling you that? Your
years of investigative experience?
- You know,I just-I listened to her,that's
all. - Let me tell you something,okay.
Just because a pretty girl tells
you a story doesn't mean it's true.
If she'd gone to trial, the burden
of proof would be on the prosecution,
yet her own lawyer told
her to take the deal.
Not to mention that
innocent people don't run.
I think this fell out of
her purse. I found it here.
- Why are you telling me this now?
- Because you were mad at me before.
So your answer to that is to delay
giving me important information?
- Well,when you put it like that.
- Okay,I got to smooth things over with the DOJ.
That phone is our only lead. Try not
to lose it before I get back. Okay?
******
Becky,there's been a slight
hiccup on the Gabby stone business.
I don't want to hear about any
hiccups. Did she sign the deal or not?
Well,she was about to.
My associate left her alone
for a second, and she took off.
- Gabby stone's in the wind?
- "In the wind"? Really?
The woman isn't a world-class
felon. She'll turn up.
Well,it better be soon,or the deal's off
the table and I'm going after your clients.
That's funny. I don't think so.
The sec decided they had no case,
and their burden of proof is lower.
If you had something on my clients,
you would have charged them already.
Harvey,I went out on a limb for you.
You make me look bad on this,
I promise you,you'll regret it.
Donna,where the hell's Mike?
Hey,anyone know a guy named Bradley?
Ball! The guy's who
about to miss the jumper.
- Do you have a last name?
- Brickstein.
- Do I look like I have time for jokes?
- Reger.
Bradley.
Mr. reger.
Bradley reger!
Sorry,can I help you?
I'm sure you've heard about the
investigation regarding Gabby stone.
Are you with the department of justice?
I... I have several questions for you.
Did you help Gabby when she was
charged with insider trading?
Of course I did. She wasn't
just a trader. She was my friend.
I recommended a lawyer and let her borrow
some cash after you guys froze her account.
That was Henderson. He's
a stickler for procedure.
Tell me,when was the
last time you saw her?
Bradley,let me inform you that
withholding knowledge of the whereabouts
of a known fugitive is a federal
offense. Do you understand me?
Gabby came in here 20 minutes ago.
She asked to borrow my keycard to Morello
assets offices, and I gave it to her.
Well,the department
appreciates your honesty.
Oh,and,Mr. reger,put a little
arc in your jump shot,all right?
If poor shooting were a crime, I'd
be forced to arrest you right here.
It's embarrassing. Go get 'em.
Harvey,I know where she is.
What are you doing here?
I told you I'd get her.
And I would let you. I just wanted to
make sure she didn't get away again.
The water was right
outside the room,okay?
And you said innocent people don't run.
Do guilty people run back
to the scene of the crime?
You don't know what she's doing.
She could be planning on taking a baseball
bat to all these computers for all we know.
Gabby,what are you doing?
That stock was on my tip
sheet. It was on mine.
If I could find that tip sheet,
I could prove my innocence.
Is this what guilty people do?
- I know they're your clients, but can you help me,please?
- I'm sorry.
You can either come with us,
or we'll have the department
of justice bring you in.
So I meant to ask you, how did your
friend's interview go yesterday?
Theresa? She didn't get the internship.
- So how do you feel about that?
- To be honest,I'm relieved.
I mean,she would have been a daily
reminder of what I couldn't do,
that I'll never score high enough
on the lsats or get into law school.
You know,that doesn't have to be true.
It is. I need to accept that I will always
be a paralegal because of this stupid test.
- I had a hard time sleeping last night. You want to know why?
- No.
Because Gabby stone is innocent.
- Oh,I slept like a baby.
- I don't think you believe that.
You think she's innocent too.
You just don't want to pursue it.
- She's not our client.
- No,Morello is our client.
And if someone else in that office
is responsible and they do it again,
won't that put our client in jeopardy?
Ooh,yep. I'm right,and you know it.
And now you have the
responsibility to investigate.
Did you tell that guy
at the basketball court
that you were an attorney
for the department of justice?
Not explicitly.
I mean,people hear
what they want to hear.
I won't impersonate
a federal agent again.
Probably a good idea.
Oh,hey,Mike,can I give you my
roommate's cat for the weekend?
Let's get it over with. I
have some actual work to do.
No,no,no,it's not what you
think. It's just very annoying,
and I figured if you were looking after
it, the cat's as good as gone,right?
Gentlemen. What's going on?
Some sort of shenanigans?
Uh,no,it's nothing. It's
just stuff between associates.
I said,"what's going on?"
Seth's just giving me a hard time
for losing Gabby stone yesterday.
Oh,but we know at this firm that we don't
dwell on our colleagues' mistakes, right?
I mean,just because one of your fellow
associates is incompetent doesn't mean
you have to constantly remind this moron
what a careless idiot he really is,right?
You.
Harold,I called you two nights ago, and you
didn't answer your phone, which is really funny,
because you're a first-year associate, who's
lucky enough to be working here at pearson/hardman,
so,when I need to get a hold of you,
you will be reachable at all times.
I don't care if you're in a coma,
hospital that's been burning down,
your mother's about to jump
off the Brooklyn bridge,
- you will pick up your phone.
- Absolutely.
- Got it?
- Yes.
******
Okay,thanks. Can you
leave my office,please?
Harvey,once this whole
Morello thing gets fixed,
remind me to be irritated with you for
not billing more on the Swindon merger.
The fact is mergers are boring,okay?
Plus,I'm busy. Also,mergers? Boring.
How'd you get these?
Oh,you mean tickets to the royal Shakespeare
company's production of king lear?
This show was sold out the
minute these tickets went on sale.
I live for king lear.How
did you know that?
- It's my job to know that.
- But why?
Louis,your billables are outstanding.
You've landed three
high-profile clients in a month,
and I want to show you my appreciation.
And I'm very happy that you're excited.
So should we get dinner
before or after the play?
Uh,um,I-I don't know.
Jessica,do you remember when
we went to that yankee game
and you caught that foul ball
and you ate all my nachos?
Did we go to the steakhouse that
night? Oh,that was a good meal.
Have a good time.
- You know what,Louis,dinner after.
- I'll have Norma make a reservation.
Fantastic.
Dean,Gabby stone's still making
noises about these tip sheets.
She insists that she had a different
sheet on the day she bought Lunardi.
She was lying.
I understand,but,after she broke
into your offices last night,
the DOJ might be inclined to
start rattling cases again.
So,for the record, you're
telling me the truth,right?
Harvey, you work for me,remember?
Well,as your lawyer,I need to be able
to tell the DOJ we're all aboveboard.
- Of course.
- So you won't mind if I look around for myself?
We've had a clean record for 50 years.
Please,Harvey,look around.
Why is that on my desk? 'Cause
the lsats are a week from Saturday.
- Great. Go away. I'm busy.
- There are only four tests a year,which means,
if you miss this one,you're gonna
have to wait another three months.
I can do math too, good will hunting.
- When did I say I was ready to retake the
lsats? - I thought that,after our talk--
Nothing about our talk said I'm
interested in bombing the test again.
- You're not gonna bomb it again.
- How do you know?
Because the first time you took it,you
were missing one essential ingredient...
- Me.
- Not interested.
If I let you help me,
will you leave me alone?
- Okay.
- I'll see you later. Get excited.
Hey,I forget,why are we
looking into Gabby stone again?
Oh,right,because I said she's
innocent, and now you agree with me.
No,I don't agree with
you that she's innocent,
but,if there's even the slightest
chance that someone else is involved,
they're putting the whole company
at risk, and I can't have that.
Okay,so you disagree
with what we agree about?
Oh,I'll agree with that.
- I don't feel sorry for Gabby stone at all.
- Because?
I found her. I was her immediate
supervisor. I nurtured her.
Then she tries to cheat
and give us a bad name.
How commonplace would
you say cheating is here?
It's not. It's not the
kind of shop we run.
So when miss stone made the trade and the
investment tripled in value, you weren't suspicious?
My job's not to worry about the
traders that are making money.
My job's to worry about
the traders who aren't.
So how exactly does the
tip sheet system work?
Our technical analyst predicts stocks that are
likely to have larger-than-expected volatility.
These predictions are handed out to our traders
on a daily basis in the form of a tip sheet.
All these traders get
the same tip sheet?
Exactly. They're printed on red
paper, so they can't be copied.
Every trader is responsible for returning
their sheet at the end of the day,
- so they can be shredded.
- So no records exist?
We keep electronic copies.
I'll need to see those
copies for the last year.
- I thought you might. I'm assuming you own a computer.
- One more thing.
I'll need to see a list of all the trades
Morello assets made in the last year.
- Well,I can't give you that.
- Why not?
Tip sheets have expired.
But our current positions-That's
proprietary information.
And I can't release
that on just your say-so.
That's not a request. We
need to protect the company.
And we're covered under
attorney-client privilege.
And I'm telling you
I'm not giving you shit.
You think I don't know what
attorney-client privilege is?
You know,you corporate lawyers
look down your noses at us
because we didn't go
to Ivy league schools.
Just because I don't have a fancy degree doesn't mean
you get to come into my house and order me around.
And you go whine to Morello and I'll knock
you on your ass like the pussy you are.
Well,Sam,I'm sorry
that you feel that way,
but I've been working for your boss
Dean Morello for a very long time,
and let me tell you something.
You try to stonewall me, you'll be
out on the street in less than a week.
As for the other stuff, do I
think that I'm smarter than you?
You're damn right I do.
But if you think that means that I can't
kick your ass up and down this floor,
take a swing and see what happens.
I didn't think so.
That was amazing.
It was like he was Mr.
t and you were rocky,
but not like rocky at the beginning
when he was all scared of Mr. t,
but at the end, when he was all like,
"ooh,give it your best shot." You know?
"Adrian!" Yes!
That's funny,but you might want
to wipe that grin off your face.
What? Why?
Because without those trades, we don't have
shit,and your little girlfriend's gonna rot in jail.
And by the way,you got
to work on your Stallone.
You need a lower register.
That was an incredible Stallone.
I've been doing that since I
was a kid,and you can't touch it.
Don't do that with food in your mouth.
No,I swallowed it.
There's food in your mouth.
- "Adrian."
- That's disgusting.
- Come on. You got this one.
- It's "A".
No,it's "C". Actually,it's
"D". It's definitely "D".
- Final answer?
- Yes,"D".
It's "A".
Rachel,you got to remember they're asking
why the argument is most vulnerable.
I can make the case that
they're all vulnerable arguments.
You could,but your first instinct
was "A". You got to go with your gut.
Right.So what if my gut can find
the exception where "a" is wrong.
- What am I supposed to do then?
- You ignore it.
I can't. That's easier said than done.
- The test isn't trying to trick you,Rachel.
- But sometimes it is,Mike.
- Well,you got to let that go.
- I can't.
- Why not?
- 'Cause I don't want to get any questions wrong.
Okay. I think we found your problem.
You're so afraid of getting
fooled by a few trick questions
that you're letting it mess
you up with all the other ones.
Look,Rachel,you want to get into
Harvard, you need a 170. Okay?
If you let a few of these trick
questions go, you're gonna be fine.
But if you keep trying to be perfect,
you're gonna overthink this whole thing.
You're gonna end up with a 130.
Rachel. Nobody gets
all the trick questions.
What about you?
First grade, they gave me an achievement
test. I scored in the 99th percentile,
so they kept giving me achievement tests
all the way up to the eighth grade level.
And I kept getting in the 99th
percentile with every one of 'em.
You couldn't get the 100th?
There is no 100th.
Next question. Come on.
- King lear.
- I happen to like king lear.
And unlike some people I know, Louis's
references don't begin and end with top gun.
Hey,I love Louis,and I don't care what
you say,I am not leaving my wingman.
See,that's funny,because
that's from top gun.
He's a wild card. Flies
by the seat of his pants.
Think I can't quote top gun.
Get the hell out of here.
Oh,that was good.
Hey,Mike. Burt Kimball's
coming to see me.
- I need you in the meeting.
- Oh,the number two at Morello?
Bet he's coming to yell at you after
your big showdown there yesterday.
If you need me,I got your back.
Thinking about finally
going to law school?
- Oh,no,I'm helping Rachel study.
- Pretty paralegal. Got it.
Okay. It's not like that.
It's exactly like that.
Oh,that reminds me.
How did you manage to
take the lsats for a woman?
- What do you mean?
- We took the test the same day.
She signed my name on
hers,and I signed hers on mine.
- Why? What's so funny?
- I just pictured you in drag.
I could pull that off.
I've got soft features.
I want to apologize
for Samuel's behavior.
He's had a chip on his shoulder ever since the department
of justice investigated miss stone's malfeasance.
He's very protective of the firm.
That's a good man to
have in your corner.
Well,so are you.
In these folders,you'll find every trade
made by Morello assets in the last year.
Personally delivered by
Burt Kimball,I'm flattered.
Well,we just want to make sure
you've got everything you need,Harvey.
We really appreciate your diligence.
Now I better get back to the office.
The Australian markets
are just opening up.
Good to see you. Always a pleasure,Burt.
Harvey,this is great.
We can take these tip sheets and
put them-- What are you doing?
This guy's not that friendly to his own
mother. He's hiding something,and I'm pissed.
- What are you talking about?
- Those aren't the real trades.
Okay. So how do we get them?
Right. How do I get them?
- Hello?
- You figure out how to get the most profitable trades yet,Mike?
The Morello brokers hang out at a bar
called the closing bell.I'm on my way now.
Good. Remember you're working.
I'll talk to you later.
Can I get a beer?
Thanks.
Hey,hey,hey,what's up,toolbox?
Oh,man. You know,you drink that beer any
slower,I'm gonna have to get you a nipple.
- Do I know you?
- Vince Landis,Morello asset.
- Yeah,that's me.
- Yeah. Russell Ginther.
The Ginth. The Ginthesizer.
- What are you talking about?
- Come on,Gervich investments.
Man,we got shithoused here a couple weeks
ago. I have no idea what you're talking about.
You,me,Pepiol,Causwell, Williamson.
That guy,dick. You
still owe me 20 bucks.
- Yeah,right.
- Russell.Right,Russell.
You still begging for scraps over
there at Gervich or what? You wish.
Hey,I need a shot. What is this?
No,drink mine,please.
Jaeger? You're better than that,man.
Money!
God,you guys are a bunch of pussies.
I guarantee you my biggest trades kick
the ass out of your biggest trades.
I don't think so,brother.
Last month,I made $2 million
on Cahill metal in one hour.
$2 million? I made $4 million off
of Montroluxx back in February.
That stock tripled over night.What's up?
$4 million? Oh,that's adorable.
How about the $6 million I just
cleared on Rypien micro devices.
Oh,yeah? What do you think my boy
here made on Piper web systems?
- What,this guy?
- Right here.
Uh,I don't know. A pack of chewing
gum and your sister's panties.
Oh,it's on.
Vince Landis! $7 million
off of Drogin limited.
$8 million off of Epling RTX.
$9 million off of RMA
integrated products.
- Well,gentlemen,greed is good.
- So is his sister. Right?
Come on,man. That's his
sister. That's not cool.
Dude,you just made,like,the same joke.
Hey,Bradley's finally here.
Uh,all right,ladies. Listen,I
got to split. It's been real.
- I'll get drinks next time,all right?
- Right.
Make money,money,make money.
- Harvey. I got the trades.
- Good. We'll talk tomorrow.
- What? No. I'm coming over no
- You're drunk.
- Do not come over.
- All right. Cool. I'll see you in a minute.
Harvey,come on. We got
to save Gabby. Gabrilini.
- Oh,you got a sweet place,dude.
- Don't ever call me dude.
Do you think that maybe I could take it off
your hands, like,when you go out of town?
Like a house-sitting-type
situation?
Remind me to have Donna
get you a spare key.
- You have the trades?
- Tada.
- Good.
- Hey,when can we...
I'm still upset that I
didn't get the internship.
- It would have been so much fun to work together, don't you think?
- Oh,absolutely.
Let me ask you something.
How did you turn it
around with the lsats?
- What do you mean?
- Well,come on.
You took 'em,didn't do so well,
and now you're at Harvard law.
It's exactly what I want to
be doing. So you can tell me.
What'd you do,sleep with the grader?
What?
I paid someone to take them for me.
- What?
- There's this guy.
I heard about him from
a friend of a friend's.
Paid him 1,000 bucks and
he took the lsats for me.
- He got me a 172.
- You cheated on the lsats?
When we were paralegals,we were
smarter than half the associates.
Why should I be denied my chance
because I can't pass some stupid test?
I'm living my dream,Rache.
I'm not gonna apologize
for it to anyone.
Come on. Come on.
- Hello?
- Mikey,yo,it's Scott.
Scott? How are you,man? I
haven't talked to you in forever.
Are you still taking lsats for other
people? I got a customer for you.
No,man. I'm not in that
business anymore.I'm sorry.
Trust me. You want to take this
meeting,dude. This chick is smoking hot.
- What's her name?
- Rachel Zane.
- You didn't give her my name,did you?
- No. Of course not.
I'm not taking that meeting,man.
What do you want me to sign now?
A confession that I killed Kennedy?
I'm not gonna pretend to be
your best friend,miss stone.
But my interests happen to be aligned
with yours right now, so please sit down.
Your colleagues' most profitable trades.
Why are you showing them to me?
Every single one of them comes from stocks
that Morello assets didn't officially recommend.
This is either a hell of a coincidence,
or these traders were all
given different tip sheets.
So you believe me when I said my tip
sheet had Lunardi pharmaceuticals on it.
Well,I'm getting there, but
you got flagged by the DOJ.
And no one else at Morello
did, so I want to know why.
What's different here?
None of these trades are for more than $9
million. That's Morello's recommended amount.
And your Lunardi purchase
was for $10 million.
Maybe someone figured out that any trade
under $10 million wouldn't draw DOJ attention.
Why'd you make a trade for $1 million
more than the recommended amount?
Look at me. I'm not
exactly fraternity material.
It's a cutthroat world, and
I wasn't performing well.
So I took a chance,and
I tried to hit it big.
I picked the wrong trade.
Gabby,if you knew you were innocent,
then why didn't you fight this harder?
After I saw how much money the
trade made, I suspected something.
I went to Burt Kimball,
he reassured me that I made a
profitable trade and did nothing wrong.
He even told me I had a $300,000
bonus coming at the end of the quarter.
I should have gone to
someone, said something.
I made one mistake, and I'm gonna
regret it for the rest of my life.
Scott. Yeah,it's Mike Ross.
This Rachel Zane,tell
her I'll take the meeting.
- Just don't tell her my name.
- Who's that on the phone?
It's nothing.
- You thinking about Gabby?
- I'm thinking about her lawyer.
- What?
-  Knowing what she said,
why would that Zegan guy agree to a deal that puts
his client behind bars without even putting up a fight?
- I can't stand that kind of shoddy work.
- It's like the bad version of both of us.
He doesn't care about his client
and he's not about winning.
He's got even less style than you.
I don't really see how
that's relevant.Like at all.
- Hold on. How did she get this lawyer?
- Her friend Bradley.
- The one who also works at Morello?
- Yeah.
I don't think Bradley's as good
a friend as she thinks he is.
Here's what you're gonna do.
I looked into it. You were right.
Put this together fast.
- I care about Gabby.
- You were right too.
You want me to go with you?
I'm sorry,but I got to take
care of this one myself.
Rachel?
What are you doing
all the way over here?
This guy has the best soft pretzels
in town. Do you want to try it?
No,I'm good. Hey,how are
you feeling about the lsats?
I was really happy with all
the prep we did yesterday.
- I'm really excited for you.
- You're excited for me?
- Why do you even care?
- I was just asking
. Well,just stop asking. Look,I came down
here because I just want to be by myself
and I bump into you,and the first thing
you want to talk about is the lsats.
Hey,sorry.
The truth is,I came down
here to clear my head too.
- About what?
- Gabby stone.
The girl who did the insider trading?
She actually suspected that
something was wrong after the trade,
but she didn't do anything about it.
She didn't want to
jeopardize her career.
Now she's gonna be paying for that
mistake for the rest of her life.
Anyway,I'm sorry I ruined your alone
time. I'll see you back at the office.
Let me ask you something,Nick.
- Does Burt Kimball drag his feet paying you too?
- Excuse me?
'Cause in my experience,getting money from
that asshole is like getting blood from a stone.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Yes,you do.
See,after I saw your client
sitting in jail,I got to wondering.
How'd she find you?I'm
gonna call security.
Absolutely. See,it turns out that
her friend Bradley recommended you.
Bradley,who's been at Morello
assets for the past seven years.
So I checked. You know what I found?
You represented Burt Kimball
in a civil suit 12 years ago.
It just so happens you also represented Lunardi
pharmaceuticals in their fda approval proceedings.
That doesn't mean anything.
You've seen my relationship with the DOJ.
Want me to point them in your direction?
Or do you want to admit to me
that Burt Kimball's paying you off?
Harvey, I don't understand.
I thought all this
business was done with.
It's almost sorted out,Dean. I'm just
here to let you know that Burt's a crook.
- What did you say?
- Harvey.
He used a lawyer to periodically
provide him with insider information.
Once he got this information,
he handed out one tip sheet
different from all the others,
so the trader,in this
instance,Gabrielle stone,
would make a trade not knowing that
she was acting on an illegal tip.
It was actually ingenious.
If the trade was ever under suspicion,
even the trader couldn't point to Burt.
- We've heard more than enough,thank you.
- I don't think so.
Miss stone made two mistakes.
One,she made a trade
for more than $9 million.
And the other was not going to the DOJ.
The second the stock
shot up through the roof.
- You son of a bitch.
- Harvey,this is a lot to digest.
Well,I'll make it easy for
you,Dean. He's a cancer.
You don't cut him loose,he's
gonna kill your whole company.
How dare you walk in here and
accuse me with these things?
I mean,you are my lawyer.
No,Burt,I'm the lawyer for
Morello asset management.
As far as the law is concerned,
Dean Morello's my client,not you.
- Dumb son of a bitch.
- Burt,you're fired.
What? Effective immediately.
You're gonna fire me? Because of this?
I hope you're happy. 'Cause without
me,this hedge fund's nothing.
I'll be happy when the department of
justice puts your ass in handcuffs.
Enjoy your freedom,Burt,because
they're coming for you.
And since you're a bigger
trophy than Gabrielle stone,
you're gonna get a whole
lot more than 11 months.
Harvey,I want you to know that
I knew nothing about any of this.
Dean,when I was 13 years old,
my little brother was getting
bullied by a kid in the neighborhood.
One day,I confronted the kid's father.
He told me he didn't know anything
about it. You know what his problem was?
It was his goddamn job to know.
Thanks for getting me out.
- We're just sorry we couldn't get you your bonus.
- It wasn't mine to begin with.
- But without it,I don't know how I'm gonna pay you.
- Don't worry about it.
Dean Morello's footing this bill.
You believed in me.
I can't tell you how
grateful I am to both of you.
Never doubted you for a second.
Oh,Gabby,I wanted to give you something.
Left it on your desk.
Thank you.
All right,well,I'm
gonna find some water.
You don't come back soon, we're
sending out a search party.
- You never doubted her for a second?
- I didn't doubt her for a second.
- I doubted her for days.
- Yeah,that's not what you just led her to believe.
People hear what they want to hear.
Oh,I meant to ask you, that big
guy that you got in a fight with,
Mr. t,was he in on this whole thing?
No,he was just a dick.
That was the most brilliant portrayal
of king lear I have ever seen.
"Come up between the
dragon and his wrath."
That was... Thank you for
tonight,Jessica,really.
- This was nice. This is really,really nice.
- You're welcome,Louis.
And,yes,this was-This was really nice.
Listen,I just want you to know how much I
appreciate everything that you do for this firm.
- I take a lot of pride in my work.
- I know,and you're very good at what you do.
Okay,can you just please say
that once in front of Harvey?
Louis,I know you and
Harvey have a rivalry.
And the truth is that,right now,
Harvey is more valuable to the firm.
But that doesn't always mean
that he is going to be on top.
Because another truth is is that I can't
always count on Harvey to listen to me,
- but I can count on you.
- Yeah. Yes,you can.
So you keep doing what you're
doing,Louis, and you're gonna be just fine.
And if he doesn't know it already,
I promise Harvey is going to understand
just how valuable you are to me.
- You know,next week there's a revival of cats.
- No.
Nice touch. Tickets to the yankee
game. Found 'em on my desk.Can't wait.
- You're welcome.
- Nachos are on you this time.
Oh,those tickets aren't for you
and me. They're for you and Louis.
Sunday the 20th. Did I mention
that I'm busy that night?
I know you are. You're busy going
to the yankee game with Louis.
Son,your ego's writing checks
that your body can't cash.
Oh,see,that's funny,because now I'm
quoting top gun and-Get out of my office.
Very funny. Very funny.
Very funny.
Mike. Hey,you got a second? I
just-I just want to thank you.
- Thank me for what?
- For going out of your way to help me with the lsats.
It's nothing. I'm sure
you'd do the same for me.
I put a lot of pressure
on myself. I always have.
You're right. I'm a perfectionist.
- It's okay.
- No,it's not okay.
My dad,he always wanted a son.
Never something that they brought
up. It was just sort of there.
And I never felt like I
was good enough for him.
Which is why I don't like to put
myself in positions where I might fail.
So I decided to just push the lsats,
give myself a little more time to study.
That's good. That's great. I
think you made the right choice.
Really? Why?
You were the one that's been
pushing me to take them next week.
I just meant that I,you know,
support the decision you made.
Why are you suddenly changing your tune?
Because if you're not
ready,you're not ready.
- Listen,I got to go. I'll see you tomorrow.
- No,that's not why.
All that interest in Theresa and then
the other guy didn't show up,but you did.
- You were gonna take the test for me.
- What guy? What are you talking about?
You know exactly what I'm talking
about. You're the test genius,right?
Mike,I could pick up the
phone and find out right now.
Yes,I took the test
for your friend Theresa.
That's the whole reason
you were trying to help me.
- Because you thought if you didn't, you were gonna get caught.
- That's not true.
How am I supposed to believe that?
Honestly,how am I supposed
to believe anything you say
when the whole time you were at
Harvard studying to be a lawyer,
you were actually
cheating for other people?
- Yes,I was helping people
cheat,okay,but-- - But what?
It's not the whole story.
www.tvsubtitles.net