[Overlapping chatter]
I just don't understand.
Yeah, there's a lot of
things you don't understand.
Everyone is wearing a black tie.
And, you're wearing a gray tie.
This is acceptable
at a black tie affair.
There's nothing wrong with
the tie that I'm wearing.
- Thank you--
- Yes, please.
Champagne, sir?
Is it?
From the region?
In France?
Because if it's not,
it's called sparkling wine,
and I don't really drink
sparkling wine.
- Forget it.
- Forgive him.
His parents really wanted
a girl.
Never got over it.
Wait a minute.
You can taste the difference.
I'm not being a snob.
Not a snob?
You sound like Frasier's
brother.
Niles Crane
was completely misunderstood.
Okay, boys,
you don't want me
to give you a time-out now,
do you?
Look, I'd be willing
to stand
in a corner if you agree
to paddle his bottom.
That's hilarious.
I'm just saying that if they
want us to donate
to their charity,
they might as well step it up.
You know, make me want
to give away my money.
Your money?
You're here representing
the firm, Louis.
And we've always
been committed
to giving back
to the community.
Jessica,
is that--
Tori.
Yes, and I owe her a call.
Excuse me.
Do I smell like sausage?
No more than usual.
Why?
Uh, because I'm about to meet
the future Mrs. Louis Litt.
I had pizza before I came
and I just want to make sure
I still am not emanating
any aroma.
Oh, you're emanating
something.
It's called pheromones
and women find it irresistible.
Watch this.
Harvey.
You remember Tori?
Of course.
Nice to see you.
I told Jessica I don't really
want to talk shop
while we're here
to support a good cause.
Well, that's the beautiful
thing about a retainer.
We're always on call
when you need us.
So how can we help?
It involves one of our most
trusted senior VPs.
Something recently came
to light about his past
and I'm shocked by it,
really.
You tell us where it hurts
and we'll make it go away.
Oh!
Uh...Ooh.
Wait.
- Wait?
- Yeah.
Well, it's just...
This feels like it's moving
really fast.
I should slow down?
No, I just--I mean,
like--
I just got out of
a relationship and...
Right.
You kind of did too.
I wasn't really seeing anyone.
You know what I mean.
Trevor.
Yeah, Trevor.
Right.
Trevor.
Um, ahem.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
We should slow down.
[Both sigh]
I should make us some tea.
- You want some tea?
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
Yeah, let's drink some tea.
Thank you.
What's the, uh,
Harvard Club?
Oh, it's, uh--
it's, like, this clubhouse
for Harvard alumni.
Yeah, that invite is, uh--
it's for this networking
thing for lawyers.
I got it at work.
Hmm, would you go?
What?
Are you kidding me?
No.
I have a hard enough time
pretending at work.
It's not like I want
to enter the lion's den.
[Sighs]
Well, if you were
gonna go...
and you were gonna
take a date--
It would be you.
I'd love to take you.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh!
Who's moving too fast now?
Oh, well, that's due to saying
all the right things.
Oh.
[Chuckles]
[Cell phone rings]
Hey, what's the emergency?
Couldn't find a date
to the prom?
We're firing Stan Jacobson.
Who?
Senior Vice President,
Drybeck Accounting.
- Our accounting firm?
- Yes.
They're our firm
and our client.
How's that possible?
They signed a conflict
of interest waiver.
Look at that.
He's actually learning
how the law works.
Acquaint yourself with
Drybeck's company charter
and Stan's original
employment contract.
- What'd he do?
- He lied.
He lied?
About what?
Wait, let me guess.
He cooked the books.
God, doesn't anyone
on Wall Street
put in an honest day's work
anymore?
Actually, he's got
a stellar record as a Senior VP.
He lied on his resume.
Never got his CPA license.
Never even went
to business school.
He lied about
where he went to school
and now he's getting fired?
Drybeck does the books
for half of Wall Street.
Word gets out that
a senior staff is a fraud,
they're gonna start
bleeding clients.
We have to do this fast
and keep it quiet.
Relax.
That's not gonna happen to you.
But I would get fired
if Jessica found out.
Found out what?
Just told me he's a virgin.
That doesn't surprise me
one bit.
All in due time, Mike.
You have those
severance quotes?
♪ Suits 1x10 ♪
The Shelf Life
Original Air Date on August 25, 2011
[Ima Robot's" Greenback Boogie]
♪ See the money wanna stay
for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feels ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive,
I don't mind ♪
♪ being busy, so I'm busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ all right ♪
♪ yes, hey, hey,
I like to dance ♪
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Oh, where you headed, doll?
Pearson Hardman
to see Mike Ross.
Uh, he expecting you?
No, I just was gonna
drop this off.
No appointment.
I can't let you up.
Do I look like a terrorist?
Do I look like I want
to lose my job?
Jenny?
Rachel.
Hey.
You here to see Mike?
Sort of.
I just--
I was gonna drop this suit
off for him.
Harvey called late last night,
some big emergency,
and Mike ended up staying
the night.
Actually, could you
help me out.
I'm running so late to work.
Sure.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Oh.
[Giggles]
Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Oh!
And can you tell Mike that
I left the key under the mat?
Absolutely.
Thank you so much, Rachel.
- You're welcome.
- You're amazing.
[Clears throat]
Ahem.
Uh!
I'm up.
Your girlfriend stopped by.
Dropped that off for you.
Girlfriend?
You guys move
in together already?
What?
No.
We--she's not my--
why do you care?
I don't.
What--
what was the big emergency
last night?
Um, Harvey.
He's firing some big vp from our
accounting firm this morning.
Stan Jacobson?
Yeah, why?
You know him?
No, he was just checking in
at reception when I got there.
What?
Oh, my God!
I got to change.
I will let him know
that you will be right there.
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
Performance numbers,
HR guidelines,
severance quotes,
and Stan's in the waiting room.
Did you sleep here
last night?
I wouldn't exactly
call it sleeping.
Where'd you get that suit?
Uh, Rachel.
No, I mean Jenny gave it
to Rachel downstairs.
She slept over last night.
Jenny did, not Rachel.
Do I really need to be here
when you fire this guy?
You want to learn how
it's done, right?
I read this guy's employment
records, Harvey.
He's smart, talented,
loyal.
Oh, and you feel bad
for him.
I'm shocked.
Where's my smoking gun?
Background check that
confirmed Stan lied
about his credentials.
It never came through.
On it.
Okay.
[Knock on door]
Come in, come in.
Um, could you help me
with something?
I need to get this fax
for Harvey and it's--
Good morning.
He needs a--
You can tell,
can't you?
I bet you everybody can.
[Giggles]
Uh, tell what?
You...wax your eyebrows?
I was with the most beautiful
woman last night.
[Scoffs]
Uh, she wax your eyebrows?
We did a lot of things
last night
and waxing wasn't
one of them,
if you know what I mean.
Oh, God.
Uh, well, that's great.
I'm here to ask--
Her name's Charisse
and we have so much in common.
And Mike,
there was like this--
there was like this,
"mmm."
Mm-mm.
- Like a "mmm."
- Mm-mm.
Like a chemical thing
would happen
when our bodies would touch.
No, I really don't want to
have this conversation with you.
Oh, come on.
We're both guys, right?
Little locker room talk
around the office.
I mean, that creates
a little male bonding.
That's crazy.
I just heard my name.
Did you hear that?
Someone's calling me.
I'm gonna--
just one second, okay?
He's probably still a virgin.
Mr. Jacobson, hi.
Mike Ross, Harvey's associate.
So sorry to keep you waiting.
Just gonna be a couple
more minutes, okay?
Okay, great.
Thank you.
Yes, I hear you.
Your office couldn't
find a copy.
Can you tell me the name
of the security firm
you guys used to do
the background check?
Okay, great.
Uh, nope.
That's great.
I found the number myself.
Thank you.
Sally, yes.
This is Mike Ross
for Pearson Hardman.
I'm calling regarding
a background check you guys did.
Uh, sure.
[Cell phone rings]
You could refuse
to cooperate,
but then you would be wrong.
Uh, Sally,
hold on one minute.
Yeah?
Uh, no.
Stan is going to be there
in two minutes.
He's in the bathroom.
Okay.
Sally, you there?
Let's do this.
Uh, I'm gonna fax you
the subpoena
that I'm holding
in my hand right now
and you can show that
to your boss and then we--
great.
Uh, let me send you
my fax number now.
Nice.
[Sighs]
Stan.
Oh, hey.
We ready?
Yes.
I'm sorry about that.
No worries.
I know you,
by the way.
7611053.
[Chuckles]
Your employee code.
See, I remember everyone
that way.
Ahh.
Anyway, you are taking me
to see Harvey.
I have been dying to meet him.
Why is that?
His balls.
His autographed ones.
I'm a huge baseball fan.
Oh, right.
Really?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No.
If I wasn't an accountant,
I would be
a major league scout.
I can tell you anything
you want to know
just by looking
at somebody's numbers.
For instance,
slugging percentage
versus strikeouts during
spring training--
Do you want
to walk and talk maybe?
Ahh.
Yeah, I could write a book.
[Clears throat]
Stan Jacobson.
Mr. Specter,
it is a pleasure.
Stan, it's nice to meet you.
- Has Mike alr--
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Is that them?
Oh!
Jeter.
Hank Aaron.
No way!
Maris?
That's not number 61,
is it?
No, but it was signed
by Tracy--
Stallard.
Ha-ha-ha!
Big baseball fan.
Stan, why don't you have
a seat over here?
Hey, why don't I get us
some waters?
Sorry.
I get talking about baseball,
I cannot stop.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, I know how valuable
your time is.
I do do the books.
And speaking of which,
your assistant tells me
you wanted to go over something
from your last audits.
I could really use a water.
Stan, we're not here to go
over any accounting business.
You're here because
you're being let go.
What?
It's not gonna feel
that surprising
when you understand why.
The firm looked into your
background recently.
They know you lied about
passing the CPA exam.
You were hired because of your
outstanding credentials
and the reality is
they never existed.
I've been there
for nine years.
My work has been
nothing but--
[scoffs]
I mean, why would this
even matter now?
You have been committing fraud
your entire career.
The liability it presents--
No!
I don't accept this.
Okay, take a deep breath.
Once you go over
the severance numbers,
you'll see that we've been
more than fair.
[Scoffs]
Fair?
You think this is fair?
We understand how difficult
this must be, Stan.
How you must feel right now.
You have no idea what
I feel right now.
Just so I'm clear--
you're not denying what we're
presenting you with?
You mean that I lied
back when Drybeck hired me?
No.
But I'm not some
scam artist either.
I did go to college.
I just...
couldn't afford to graduate.
No one ever
questioned it before
because I'm that good
with numbers.
Then they find out
all of a sudden.
They didn't.
This background check
is five years old.
What?
That doesn't make sense.
Is this the original?
Yeah.
So Tori knew...
all this time?
This is the same thing
that happened to Paula.
- Who?
- Paula.
Discovered some
undisclosed income,
the books weren't adding up,
she brought it to me.
The next thing I know,
she is gone.
I asked Tori about it,
then I start
getting shut out of meetings.
They're trying
to hide something
and they're firing me
so they can.
Hey,
where are you going?
I'm not signing
some agreement.
Are you kidding me?
I'm getting railroaded!
- Should I go after him?
- No.
You've done enough already.
So you let him leave?
Physically restraining someone
is not in my job description.
Well, what about
your associate,
the one who shared
the background check?
That was a confidential
internal document.
Stan should have never
seen it.
Why did you even have it?
You didn't expect us to fire
him without proof, did you?
Tori's right.
Stan shouldn't have seen it.
Then I'm guilty
of being thorough.
Hey, I still don't understand
why you haven't
told us the whole truth.
I mean, if you knew
five years ago,
why'd you make it sound like
this is something recent?
Because it only came
to my attention two days ago.
Then who ordered
the background check?
It's routine.
You check with human resources.
Is it routine
for human resources
to keep something from
the CEO for half a decade?
What are you insinuating?
I think what Harvey
is saying is given
how quickly we tried
to accomplish this,
some of the details
might have gotten lost.
What was also lost
is that Stan
never signed
the severance package,
which included
the confidentiality agreement,
which means if he decides
to make waves,
the whole point of avoiding
negative publicity--
Harvey will
track down Stan
and make sure that he signs
the severance package
and the confidentiality
agreement today.
You have my word.
Thank you.
Of course.
It's allight, Tori.
She's lying.
She knew about Stan.
She's known for a long time.
And that matters to us why?
Because she's taking
advantage of us.
We are being manipulated
into firing
one of her employees and told
not to ask questions.
Well, I have questions.
And the answer is ten.
As in $10 million per year--
the amount of business Drybeck
generates for this firm.
Which means you have
to finish what you started.
Find Stan and get him
to sign those documents.
Oh, and as far as
I'm concerned,
that little associate of yours
iso blame for all of this.
That was an honest mistake.
He knowingly revealed
the client's
confidential document.
That is not a mistake.
How many more chances
are you gonna give that kid?
Oh, I didn't realize
we were keeping score.
But if that's the case,
I still think
he's coming out ahead.
Whatever you're doing,
stop.
Wait, you're gonna want
to see this.
Paula O'Neil, the former Drybeck
employee that Stan mentioned,
she filed a wrongful
termination suit
that mysteriously went away.
Really?
Let me see that.
Come with me.
Wait.
Do you not think something
funny's going on?
You know what?
Here's what I think
is going on.
You're sympathizing with Stan
because you think he's you.
That doesn't mean that--
You need to learn something
from what just happened,
not the least of which
is how anyone,
no matter how valuable,
can be let go.
I can chalk up
what happened with Stan
to youthful exuberance,
but Jessica can't.
So if you want to work here,
you better go home now,
because if she sees you--
- Wait, wait.
Is she gonna fire me?
This habit of you
empathizing
with every client,
it's not getting you anywhere.
You want to work
in this firm?
You need to deal in facts,
evidence,
information that can hold up.
That's what a real lawyer does.
Stan.
Did you follow me here?
Doesn't take a sleuth
to figure out
that your next step would be
to see another lawyer.
Bopal and Williams.
They're a good firm.
Not the friendliest bunch.
They called you.
That is against lawyer-client
privilege.
No one's breaking any laws,
okay?
My assistant has a network
of other assistants
that tell her anything
she wants to know,
like when someone calls
for an emergency appointment.
You forgot this when you left.
I said I'm not
signing anything.
It's nothing to sign.
It's a lawsuit.
You worked for Drybeck
for 9 years,
oversaw 80 clients,
filed hundreds of tax returns,
and fought 27 audits.
Now, in light of your recently
discovered fraud,
all of that can now
be called into question.
Therefore, you are being sued
for nine years back pay,
plus any expenses incurred to
mitigate the damage you've done.
This is--
this would bankrupt me.
Or you can take
what's behind door number two.
- It's Aberdeen.
- Who?
It's not a "Who."
It's a "What."
Drybeck is doing business
with them
and I think that's where
the problem lies.
You don't get it,
okay?
I'm only leaving with
one of these,
and if it's
the lawsuit,
the first thing your friends
upstairs
are gonna ask you for
is a big, fat retainer.
And when you tell them
that Harvey Specter
is the one that's suing you,
you're gonna watch the color
drain from their faces.
Now what would you
like to do?
[Knock on door]
This is not cool.
You leave me in
your apartment all night
and say you're gonna
be right back.
You don't even thank me
for dropping off your suit.
I had a bad day, Jenny.
So you couldn't call me?
I almost got fired, okay?
What happened?
It--it's not worth
explaining.
Okay.
I need to find evidence
that our accounting firm
is up to something,
so I found this woman who filed
a wrongful termination suit
against them, but then
she referred me to her lawyer.
Did you call them?
Yeah, but they're
this huge firm.
Unger and Macy.
They wouldn't take my call.
Why not?
There's
a confidentiality clause
in the settlement, for one.
So?
So it means that they can't
share details like that.
You know,
I thought all lawyers
secretly shared that stuff.
You're all in the same club,
right?
What?
That's not a dumb thing
to assume.
No, no, no, no.
That's not dumb at all,
because...
We all are in the same club.
Unger and Macy have almost
as many Harvard grads
as we do,
which means--
They're gonna be
at the mixer tonight.
And there are two things
that lawyers love to do.
Drink and talk.
- Hi.
Uh, Mike Ross,
class of 2011.
Ross.
Sorry, I don't have you on here.
Do you have your I.D.?
I can run it through
the computer.
Uh, my Harvard I.D.?
What did you say your name
was again?
Michael Ross
of Pearson Hardman.
Boy, you think they ask Harvey
for his I.D.
when he comes to this place?
Harvey Specter?
You work with Harvey Specter?
Uh, yeah, yes.
I'm his associate.
I can call him if you like.
Just don't tell him
I gave you any trouble, okay?
Welcome.
Thank you.
Mmm.
Oh, God.
I'm never gonna survive this.
Deep breaths.
You'll be fine.
Hey.
I saw the signed severance
papers on my desk.
- Thank you.
- And I also left word for Tori.
Yes, we spoke.
She's relieved,
but I wouldn't go so far
as to say completely forgiving.
You ever heard
of Aberdeen Solutions?
Drybeck listed them
as a consultant firm.
They bill us every month
for their management services.
Okay.
What does that mean?
- Check with accounting.
- I did.
They can only tell me
how much we pay them,
so I called Aberdeen directly.
It's an automated
answering system.
I left six messages.
No returns.
Stan mentioned it.
Something just doesn't
feel right.
Are you saying you want
to investigate our client?
They're also our accountants.
And Tori is also a friend.
Harvey, if you got caught--
I wouldn't get caught.
I am explicitly telling you
not to do this.
Well, then I'll let you know
what I don't find
after I don't look into it.
Hey, should we get the rest
of the 2010 grads
with us for a pic?
The rest?
This is 2011. No way.
Isn't he from
the 2010 class?
No, no.
I was 2011.
You're not with us.
Yeah, Rudy...
It's Mike.
You know, we--
we hung out a bunch.
Where?
Oh, you know what?
Maybe I'm thinking about
somebody else.
Sorry about that.
Has anyone seen that guy
here before?
Hey.
I'm not having any luck.
[British accent] Wish I could
say different, love.
But it's been a Potter's Field
for me too.
What?
You get to pretend
to be someone else.
I wanted to try.
It's fun.
Accent?
Hmm.
Okay, I'll stop.
What?
You're amazing.
And that's Brian Jennings.
Who's Brian Jennings?
I saw his face on
Unger and Macy's website today.
What are you waiting for?
Go.
Hi.
Ten days
for public exposure.
Next time you need a bathroom
in Times Square,
go into a hotel.
[Gavel bangs]
Five-minute recess.
Harvey.
Long time, Anthony.
Heh.
You keep company
with the high rollers
on Center Street.
What are you doing down
in night court?
I need a favor.
What kind of favor?
One that requires access
to sealed court documents.
Can it wait till tomorrow?
I got this backlog of case--
When you came to me two years
ago in the middle of the night,
did I tell you it
had to wait till tomorrow?
My chambers.
So...this is quite
a surprise.
Who'd ever think that you and
I would on a double date?
- Excuse me?
- Oh, come on.
You had to notice when you
walked in the room.
She's absolutely gorgeous.
And she's completely infatuated
with your girlfriend.
Ah.
Come on.
Come on, I'll introduce you
to her.
Charisse, honey...
uh, this is one
of my associates, Mike Ross.
Oh, so nice to meet you.
And I'm in love with your date.
Seriously.
She's just been telling me about
her work with monkeys.
It's fascinating.
Huh?
So really,
they're as smart as us?
Oh, smarter.
I never had a chance
with him.
I need to use
the ladies' room.
Would you excuse me?
Monkeys aren't smarter
than humans, sorry.
That depends on which humans
you're talking about, I guess.
- What?
- Huh?
Name of case and rough date?
Aberdeen versus
Paula O'Neill,
say six months ago.
Oh, let's see.
Says here that they were
listed as a subsidiary
of Drybeck in a wrongful
termination suit.
That's it.
That's what I'm looking for.
I can't print this out.
I'll get tagged.
Come around.
Take a look.
Is that what you're after?
Yeah, that's it.
But what's that?
[Keyboard clicking]
That links to another
court filing
in relation to Aberdeen.
Click on it.
Says here that they filed
for dissolution...
earlier today.
The whole company?
That's what it says.
They're officially shut down.
I'm gonna need
one more favor.
I think it's great
that you found someone
not in law who works out
in the real world.
Why do you say that?
Because I'm stuck
in a suit all day
or an office or a courtroom.
I think it'd be nice
to be in nature.
Don't you, Mike?
Well, I love that
you're a lawyer.
In fact, I'd love to see
where you work sometime.
You would?
I'm not feeling so well
all of a sudden.
- No.
- Yeah.
You think we can go?
- Right now?
Now.
Yeah.
- So great to meet you.
- Lovely to meet you.
Have good night.
- Bye.
Okay, why didn't you
do that sooner?
Because...
I had to get this first.
That's the guy, right?
From the firm.
That's his employee I.D.
- He gave this to you?
- No, I stole it.
What?
Listen, you could spend all
night trying to get to the guy
or you could just go into
his firm yourself and look.
Come on.
Let's go.
[Siren wails in distance]
Yeah, I can barely keep
my eyes open myself.
Filing briefs sucks.
[Electronic beep]
You actually came.
You must be Harvey Specter.
"Joe," was it?
Your friend fill you in on
the deal that's on the table?
Let me just get it straight.
You caught him rifling
through some files,
and in lieu of calling
the police,
you want me to pay you off?
I never said that.
He did.
Oh, that's great.
This way, if I level
a charge of extortion,
it's hearsay, huh?
Ten years working
for a law firm,
you learn a thing or two,
which is good,
'cause you sure as hell don't
make a lot of money doing it.
Somehow I think you're
getting by fine.
Just saying, on the level
you guys play at,
espionage happens all the time,
which is why I know
you'll do anything
to protect your secrets.
Well actually, Joe Speena,
of 2561 Clover Lane,
Astoria, Queens,
I think we all would.
Like those tax returns
you filed jointly
for the last six years while
no longer living with your wife.
You know, the IRS
can destroy you for that.
You think you're the first
person to try to extort me, Joe?
'Cause that's the level
I play at.
Now...You're a security guard
who likes to take risks.
I like that.
So here's what we're
gonna do.
This here's
a generous donation
to Joey junior's
little league team.
Now, if it gets to them,
it gets to them.
If it doesn't,
it doesn't.
But the next time we talk,
it's gonna be me
who wants a favor.
Officer.
Do I really
need to pay you back?
Let's start
with an explanation.
You said I needed
to find evidence,
so I went to find some.
By breaking into
another law firm?
Is that really worse than
paying off a security guard?
Okay, first of all,
I didn't pay him off.
Second of all,
if I hadn't paid him off,
you'd be in jail right now.
You think I might
be right about Stan.
No, I never said
you were wrong.
I said we needed evidence.
But did you find something?
Drybeck bought
a shelf company 13 months ago.
What's a shelf company?
It's a corporation
that exists only on paper,
so its owners can hide
their assets.
Isn't that a shell company?
No, it's a shelf company.
Okay, take a shell company,
give it a bank account,
credit history, tax returns,
and let it season for years
on a shelf.
Someone buys it,
slots their name into it,
and they walk away with
an established corporation
with a preexisting history.
Anyone looks any closer,
they shut it down
and do it again.
That's legal?
Shelf companies are legal.
I'm guessing what Tori's
doing with hers isn't.
Wait a minute.
Is it called "Aberdeen"?
Yeah, I saw it on the top
of this list
with 37 other
management companies
all related to Drybeck in
that wrongful termination suit.
When we get back
to the office,
I want you to find
legal precedent
that will allow us
to subpoena the records.
Okay, on it.
Do I really have
to pay you back?
Every penny.
Wait a minute.
How much was in that envelope?
Hey, what are you all doing
at my desk?
Dude, you got to check
this out.
Excuse me.
Is that Louis?
Uh-huh.
In the lobby.
Is this a security camera?
A live feed?
- What are you guys doing?
- No, no.
This is from last night.
The guys in security emailed it
up to Louis this morning.
And why are we watching it
on my computer?
Well, we're not gonna risk
watching it on one of ours.
And everyone knows
your password.
How does everybody
know my password?
"Ross999."
How hard is that to crack?
Okay, "999" increases
the odds of--
Oh, shh!
Here it comes.
[All gasp]
What?
[Laughter]
[All exclaim]
Oh, no.
What did he say to her?
Oh, evidently Louis wants
a restraining order
and he needs this
as evidence.
Oh.
What?
Uh, um, it--
okay, listen.
Please don't.
I came in here and it--
look, I--
are you okay now?
Louis?
If the message you left
was another trick
to get me down here--
No tricks, I assure you.
Come on in.
Stan, I'm Jessica Pearson.
Oh, yeah.
I know who you are.
You said if I accepted
the severance agreement,
there wouldn't be a lawsuit.
Well, there is one,
but not against you.
With you.
We know about Aberdeen.
We know what Tori
was orchestrating.
And with your help,
we can expose her.
Why should I help you?
What have you got to lose?
[Scoffs]
Tell me what you
need me to do.
Hey.
What does he have you
trying to find this time?
You really want to know?
Uh, I managed
to get a look at some files
involving our accounting firm.
What's up with
our accounting firm?
They're stealing from us.
You know your phone bill?
You have all those surcharges,
you have no idea what they mean,
but you pay 'em anyway.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, Drybeck's doing
the same thing to us,
except all their charges
are a complete scam.
Pretty sure the phone
charges are a scam too.
Yeah, maybe.
So what do you need?
I need a legal reason
to get those files
without saying
I saw those files.
You need them for court
or you just need them?
Why?
You said you read 'em,
right?
Yeah.
So then you already
have them...
in here.
You're right.
I do.
Yes, so you dictate,
I'll type.
What?
You'd actually do that for me?
They're stealing from us.
Person Hardman is my firm too.
Come on.
Okay.
With the party
of the third part,
hereto referred
to as Norton LLC--
[overlapping dialogue]
any claim that might
reasonably be anticipated--
we acknowledge that such
appointment
is irrevocable
and shall be deemed--
lawfully invested with
the power to make such contracts
or to perform acts from which
can be lawfully implied.
That's it.
Did we get it?
Saving and wait for it...
Done.
Oh.
[Sighs]
[Both chuckling]
What?
Your mind.
It's just--
it's amazing.
Thanks.
What?
Your mind's amazing too.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Who you calling this late?
Oh.
She's waiting up for you?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
It's pretty late.
She's probably sleeping
by now.
I'll just text her.
It's tough to have
a relationship
with the first year
or any year.
You just don't have a life.
How'd you make it work?
Who said I did?
It's--it's impossible
to have anything long-term
unless you find someone
that has the same
80-hour work week
and then...
that doesn't work either,
because they're busy too.
Yeah, well, I'm not gonna
let that be the reason
that Jenny and I don't--
What are you two
still doing here?
- Uh, it's for Harvey.
- Nothing.
- Uh, but we're done.
- Good night.
- Yeah, I'll see you later.
- Bye.
[Clears throat]
I'm sure you're aware
of this,
but, um, I'm just gonna
remind you anyway.
Um, this office frowns upon
relationships in the workplace.
Yeah.
Oh, God!
I'm so sorry.
That's okay.
Um...Hey.
Uh, thank you for last night.
The typing.
- Of course-- right.
- Yeah.
- Absolutely.
- It was really helpful.
Mm-hmm.
[Cell phone rings]
Um, hold on one second.
Sorry.
Hello?
I said I needed you
in my office.
And I said I was
on my way.
Save it.
Those the files?
Yes, take them, please.
Stan is in my office.
Meet us in
the conference room.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
That's okay.
I got your email
with a list of other law firms.
I respect your effort
to make amends
by referring new clients.
That wasn't a list
for client referrals.
Those are firms you should
consider for representation.
We're no longer
your attorneys, Tori.
What?
We have no choice really.
It would be impossible
to represent you
when we plan on suing you
for every penny you've got.
Is this a joke?
Aberdeen Solutions.
Created in June of 2006.
Sold to Drybeck 2010.
Dissolved two days ago.
Before that,
it was Bolton Finances.
And before that,
it was Norton Services,
Littleton LLC.
Where did you get those?
We know what you did, Tori.
You couldn't have subpoenaed
these files.
And yet we have them.
Take a look.
They're all there.
- And now we have proof.
- Proof of what?
Those are all legitimate
corporations used for--
Stealing money
and lining your own pockets.
But don't take my word for it.
Guys?
Hello, Tori.
Yeah, we hired Stan to do
a little independent consulting
on our behalf
and he's come
with some very interesting
connections.
It was easy, even if I don't
really have a degree.
There was that vacation
you invited me on last year...
to your new house
in the Bahamas.
A house you bought with money
you stole from this firm.
My firm.
Jessica--
"Jessica" what?
You can't use any of this.
We have attorney-client
privilege.
With Drybeck Accounting,
yes.
With the shelf companies?
No.
And unfortunately for you,
you're listed
on the shelf companies.
You stole from me.
You either come clean now
or the only time
you'll see your children
in the next decade
will be during prison
visiting hours.
So I'm gonna get
my job back now, right?
I don't see why not.
No, Stan, you're not.
What?
Drybeck's going bankrupt
after this all shakes out.
Even if they don't,
they're not gonna hire you back.
Why?
Because you falsified
your resume.
What am I supposed
to do now?
Well, we just got your more
than your severance package.
I suggest you use it
to tide yourself over
till you figure something out.
Stan...Hey.
Your best asset is your mind.
They can't take that from you.
One little mistake.
You could go back to school,
become legitimate.
Start over?
I never should have done it.
[Sighs]
Told you they wouldn't
catch me.
What are you looking for,
Harvey?
- Positive reinforcement?
- Nothing major.
A trophy,
Nobel.
Would your likeness in bronze
in the lobby be okay?
Bust or life-size?
You did a good thing,
Harvey.
Well, it wasn't just me,
you know?
Well, then I guess
I should give the kid
the benefit of the doubt
from now on.
You should.
Well, you'll be happy
to know
that Stan has no idea
what he's gonna do
with the rest of his life.
That doesn't make me happy.
Well, what if I tell you
I have no idea
what I'm doing with mine?
What the hell are we gonna do
when I get caught, Harvey?
You're not gonna get caught.
That's your answer?
What else is there?
Why?
What?
Hire me.
Why would you do that to me?
You mean for you.
No, I don't.
You made it perfectly clear
that you only do things
for yourself.
So why?
You mean the reason why
I became a lawyer
or your friend dealt drugs
or you used to cheat?
I cheated because I needed--
You couldn't make money
any other way?
Bullshit.
Life is this.
I like this.
That's not me.
Well, if it wasn't me,
you wouldn't be here.
So if you want this to stop,
all you got to do is tap out.
- Hello.
- Oh.
You're here to see Mike.
We're gonna celebrate
his victory.
Ah.
You know, I actually think
that it's a really,
really good idea that
you've come to pick him up.
In fact, if I were you,
I'd do it a little
more often.
Just all those late nights
working with Rachel.
What do you mean?
What do I--
[Laughs]
Well, come on.
You're a smart girl.
You understand animal behavior.
I think you can
figure it out.
Hey.
You ready?
Yeah.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net