[Indie rock music]
♪ ♪
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
You know there are easier ways
to kill me,
if you're worried
I'll rat you out
for cheating on the LSATs.
- What? Come on, Rachel.
- Unbelievable.
Rachel!
[Murmurs]
Rachel, come on,
let me buy you a fresh cup.
Are you actually
gonna buy it this time,
or are you gonna steal it?
Okay, first of all,
I don't steal, I cheat.
There's a big difference.
And I don't do it anymore.
Oh, great defense.
I'm sorry, Your Honor,
I know that I murdered her,
but I promise
I won't do it anymore.
Look, I understand
why you're mad,
but I still don't think
you're being entirely fair.
Not fair? What's not fair
is that you repeatedly
help people skirt a system
that stands in the way
of me becoming a lawyer.
You know what?
Why don't you give up
the whole Saint act,
since the only reason
you figured out I was cheating
is 'cause you were thinkin'
about cheating yourself.
Thinking about cheating
and actually doing it
are two very different things,
Doctor Analogy.
Oh.
[Scoffs]
Whoa! Wait,
did I miss an apocalypse?
Where is everyone?
You know,
for someone
with a freak brain,
you manage to forget everything
important.
Follow me,
but don't talk to me.
Not bad, Harvey.
The Prague hotel, in the black
in less than three years,
and a successful I.P.O.
Who said passion
wasn't productive?
I don't know anyone
that's ever said that.
- Jones, tell me something.
- Mm.
You have 30 hotels
in 12 different countries,
but you spent last week
in Daniel Vega's Lisbon resort.
What? Just, you know,
checkin' out the competition.
That was more
than a fact-finding mission.
You're thinking merger.
Do you honestly believe
that I'd do that
without talking to you first?
- I know you would.
- Then perhaps I did.
Jones, if you try
to pursue a merger,
you may not control
what happens to your business
that you built
so passionately.
Okay, Sherlock,
hear me out.
Combined, we're 100 hotels
in 23 countries.
I like
having multiple homes.
But you don't need
another name on the mortgage.
- It's a good deal.
- Yeah, and it's my job
to get you
a better one, okay?
Promise me you didn't do
a handshake deal.
Donna!
Who's ready
for mock trial 2011?
[Cheers and applause]
What, like
make-believe trials?
We gonna play
Monopoly after?
This is
your Debutante Ball.
The impression you make
on the partners will last.
- And let me guess, Harvey was--
- Oh, legendary.
Shocking.
Sydney Thompson
was a consultant
with
Lunders Global Initiative.
She had a few too many,
and decided to entertain
her friends with
an impersonation of her boss,
Lena Lunders.
This impersonation
was recorded
and uploaded onto
a social networking site.
The next day
she was fired.
Sydney is now suing
for wrongful termination.
We are looking to see
how you do under pressure.
Can't cheat your way
out of this one.
The partners
have been instructed
to only use the associates
in emergency situations.
[Whoops and applause]
[Laughs]
Let the games begin.
- Whoo!
- All right.
When your name is called, please
step up and meet your match.
I think you mean
my bitch, Louis.
[Chatter and murmurs]
Gene Kaplan.
I'm glad Jessica
finally chose a case
with a strong
female character.
Last year I was forced
to play a traffic cop.
Jocelyn Lowenstein.
It was a total waste
of my talent.
Wait a minute,
you play witnesses?
Oh, I don't play anything.
I embody. And if I'm
on your team, you're a winner.
- Well, in that case--
- No.
[Quietly]
Okay.
[Clears throat]
Mike Ross.
Kyle for the plaintiff.
[Applause]
Ross for the defendant.
May the best man win.
Oh, by the way, Kyle,
weren't you, uh,
national mock trial champion?
That's right, Louis.
In high school,
college,
and law school.
♪ Suits 1x07 ♪
Play The Man
Original Air Date on August 3, 2011
Ima Robot's Greenback Boogie
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feels ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive,
I don't mind ♪
♪ being busy, so I'm busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ all right ♪
♪ yes, hey, hey,
I like to dance ♪
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
I need an assessment
of all of Vega's hotels, okay?
I want you
to check annual earnings,
property value.
- There should be writing.
- Yeah.
This all doesn't sound
like an emergency.
The mock trial--
okay.
I'm on it.
Uh, listen, Harvey, about--
- I don't give advice.
Okay, please, sensei?
I'm out of my league
with this thing.
Listen to me.
Don't go to trial.
It's a mock trial.
I think the trial part
is kind of
a prerequisite.
All right.
Law is about control, okay?
You can only control so much
with a jury, judge,
witnesses, and another lawyer
with an ego complex.
What if the lawyer
doesn't have an ego complex?
Every lawyer
has an ego complex.
The firm has presented
an exercise
where there's potential
for failure, okay?
All I'm saying is
try and create a situation
where that's not
even a possibility.
Kobayashi Maru.
- Koba--what now?
Star Trek.
Captain Kirk.
He wins a no-win situation
by rewriting the rules.
- You're a Trekkie.
- Hey, Captain Kirk is the man,
okay? I don't wanna hear
another word about it.
Now, enough with
your fake law problem.
Let's deal with my real one.
Aye, aye, Captain.
You wanna know
how to do a cross?
Some people
like to use big words.
Some people like
to go for sympathy.
But personally,
I'm a little more go
for the groin.
Oh, hey, Mike.
[Laughter]
You mind dismissing
the peanut gallery
so we can talk, Kyle?
I'm sorry, guys.
Looks like Ross here
came to plead for mercy.
[Laughter]
Wow.
If you're here for
the witness/exhibit exchange,
don't bother.
I already
know who you're gonna call
and what evidence
you're gonna use.
Actually, I'm not gonna
call any witnesses
or present any evidence.
Let's settle.
Or I can beat you.
The plaintiff has shown
a pattern of making
derogatory statements
about my client.
- Hearsay.
- Not the emails.
Which have
no tone of voice
and are subject
to interpretation.
Which is exactly why
your argument is shaky at best.
- Then beat me in court.
- Kyle.
There's a reason that Harvey
chose me to be his guy.
Do you really wanna
find out what that reason is?
And how do I know
this isn't some sort of trick?
It's not a trick.
This is our chance
to stand out.
Look, settling gets us
in and out of there
in five minutes.
You drop the suit, and you and I
spend the rest of the week
making ourselves
indispensable to the partners
while everyone else
buries their heads
in Candyland court.
I'm going against
my better judgment
and trusting you.
So we have a deal.
Daniel,
paperwork looks good,
despite the fact that you two
decided to go lawyer commando.
The devil's always
in the details.
Harvey, I know
that impulse purchases
don't exist in your world,
but the timing was right.
And as for the details,
I'd like to leave that
to my man Scott.
Does he always
like to be late?
She.
Just got off a plane
from London.
Oh.
[Dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Meet Ms. Dana Scott.
Welcome.
- Hi. Thank you.
- Scottie.
- Harvey.
- Oh, you two know each other!
We went
to Harvard Law together.
Harvey was fifth
in the class, and I was--
oh, I forget.
What was it?
Married to the library?
That's right.
Number one.
Number one at studying.
Okay, this way.
Tell me, Scottie,
what's my success rate
against you in the real world
where we practice real law?
Oh, Harvey, there should be no
winners or losers in a merger.
Just a happy new couple.
That's right,
3 and 0.
Well, I say we let
these two talk deal points
while I try your chef's
famous sea bass.
Absolutely.
Play nice.
We like each other,
even if you two don't.
"Married
to the library"?
It's not my fault
that the library
was the best you could do.
[Scoffs]
Do you have
the preliminary proposal?
No, I just flew in from London
completely unprepared.
Try not to be intimidated.
I use some big words.
Overcompensation
isn't that big of a word.
- It isn't?
- I can hardly wait to see
the work
of a senior partner.
I see my promotion
popped up
on your Harvey Specter
Google alert.
That's not all
that's going to pop up.
[Breathing heavily]
[Thud]
Can't remember
the last time we had a bed.
Pretty convenient that we're
working on a hotel merger.
[Thud]
Mm, remember
the mining deal?
Shaft 27?
How could I forget?
Listen, about
the due diligence--
Ah, ah, ah,
Harvey.
You know the rules.
[Breathing heavily]
No case negotiations
till we're done.
I think that
might be a while.
[Chuckles]
[Upbeat music]
Couldn't resist seeing
brilliance in action, huh?
Actually,
I have to be here.
I'm playing the part
of the plaintiff.
Wow. I knew you
were pissed,
but I didn't realize
you were petty.
- What does that mean?
- It's an adjective.
It means small-minded
and spiteful.
You chose to work with the one
guy who's going against me.
- Kyle asked me, and I said yes.
- You know what?
It doesn't really matter,
'cause you're never
gonna take the stand.
Really? How's that?
It's a surprise.
But prepare to watch
a mock trial legend be born.
Is counsel ready to proceed
with opening statements?
We'd like to submit
a settlement agreement--
The plaintiff is ready,
Your Honor.
Which is it,
counselor?
Um, the counsel
for the plaintiff
and I agreed
to a settlement yesterday.
He must've misunderstood.
We had discussed,
but I never agreed
to anything.
Do you have
a signed agreement?
Uh...
[Sighs]
No.
Then we are ready
to proceed.
You have the floor.
Thank you.
On March 31, 2010,
Sydney Thompson
was unwittingly recorded
on a cell phone.
She made a joke,
the type of joke
that I'm sure every person
in this courtroom
has made at one point
or another...
[Loud whooshing,
white noise humming]
[Kyle's words distorting
at slow speed]
at fast speed]
[Muffled]
Mr. Ross.
[White noise stops]
Mr. Ross!
Are you ready?
Um, the, uh,
the defense...
[Sighing]
Uh...
According to
Bowmaster v. Whitely,
if the party to a settlement
is surprised
by the repudiation
of the settlement,
then the court must provide
a reasonable amount of time
to prepare for the trial.
- Reasonable time.
- Yes, Your Honor.
You get five minutes.
Vega has
more property.
Debeque has
more potential.
[Chuckles]
Which is harder
to monetarily define.
This isn't a library,
Scottie.
My guy's
an up-and-comer.
That's why
your guy's pouncing.
Your client
is an impulse shopper,
which is what may have
made him a quick success,
but it could make him
an even faster failure.
So he's
a passionate guy.
He falls in love with a city,
and he builds himself a hotel.
Who are you to argue
with his track record?
I'm a realist,
and I have never seen a deal
pushed through so quickly.
So what?
So your guy
might wake up tomorrow
and decide that he
doesn't wanna do this,
which is why I'm not
showing you our private books
without a signed deal.
- Is that a joke?
- Am I laughing?
Look, I may not have been
awake during our M&A Clinic--
Except for when you
were copying my notes.
Which was no walk in the park.
You write like a monkey.
But in any case,
due diligence is a requirement.
[Sighs]
I have an obligation
to my client.
Then we
don't have a deal.
And everyone's gonna know
it's because you killed it.
You know...
I don't see you rushing
to show us your private books.
I have nothing to hide.
You can have full access
to our books right now.
Great. You show me yours,
and I'll show you mine.
Don't say it, Harvey.
Mike.
Hey, are you okay?
Now you care?
Mr. Ross,
I'm gonna have to ask you
not to speak to my client.
She's not your client.
She is Rachel
the paralegal.
And I only have
five minutes,
so you should really
get out of my face.
- What's your problem, Mike?
- My problem is that you
don't have the balls
to make this a fair fight, Kyle.
Lawyering
isn't about fighting fair,
and you'd better watch
your false accusations,
or I might just sue you
for defamation.
Come on.
[Gavel bangs]
The defendant wishes
to countersue.
- On what grounds?
- I believe that's my line,
counselor.
Defamation of character.
The plaintiff's video
negatively impacted
the perception
of Lena Lunders
and impaired
her financial well-being.
That's ridiculous,
Your Honor.
In order for there
to be defamation,
the statements made
would've had to have been false.
That's not the case here.
Then you should have
no problem proving that
in court.
The countersuit
is allowed.
- Are you serious?
- Would you like
to approach the bench
and find out how serious I am?
Your Honor, the defense
should've filed counterclaims
before the trial began.
Yes, he should have.
But no one
in this crop of associates
had the foresight
to do so.
And we drafted
a whole addendum
just because we assumed
one of you would.
So I'm going
to allow it.
Do you have
a problem with that?
No, Your Honor.
This is now
a defamation trial.
You have until Friday
to prepare.
[Gavel bangs]
Nice recovery.
Thinking on your feet.
But you wouldn't
have had to
if you hadn't been
so naive.
Thank you,
Your Honor.
How'd
the negotiation go?
You come out on top?
Why didn't you tell me
Scottie was opposing counsel?
Because I didn't want you
to have performance anxiety.
About the case.
She's tough.
- You're obvious.
- And your fly's unzipped.
- No, it isn't.
- But it was earlier today.
[Gasps]
You can do better.
Ooh, is that
what Scottie said?
Type up the deal points.
I got her to cave.
Debeque's gonna run the show.
All I had to do
was show her our books.
I can't believe it.
You gave me, like,
the worst advice
anyone's ever given
another person.
Take the drama
down a notch, Juliet.
I tried to settle,
and I got completely blindsided.
I told you to settle.
I didn't tell you to be stupid.
What do you think's gonna
happen in the real world?
You have to be prepared
for anything.
Well,
in the real world,
I won't have to
be looking for someone
to play my fake witness
in my fake trial.
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you think?
Do you think witnesses
are just gonna jump up
and present themselves?
'Cause they're not.
And sometimes
when you have one,
they disappear
or recant.
And you know what you do?
You deal with it.
Mock trial
is about figuring out
what type of lawyer
you wanna be,
and there's only two types--
winners and losers.
That sounds great, Harvey,
but I haven't prepared.
I don't have anyone to play
my client or my witness,
and apparently
I'm going up against someone
that I can't trust.
Figure out
a way to beat him anyway.
Winners don't make excuses
when the other side
plays the game.
[Sighs]
Hey, Donna, I proofed
that final agreement
on the hotel merger.
Quick question--has Harvey
ever heard of spell-check?
- [Sobbing]
- Oh, my God.
- Sorry.
- Are you--
No, no, no.
It's okay. Here.
You don't have to talk.
Shh, shh, shh.
It's okay.
He says things sometimes,
and they--and they
cut to the bone.
He does it to me too.
I know, so...
It's not bad, right?
I can also do
the Demi Moore single tear--
left eye or right eye--if that's
better for the character.
Okay, I'm scared.
What's going on?
If I'm gonna play
Lena Lunders for you,
I need to be able to use
my full range of emotions.
[Sighing]
Oh, my God. I love you.
- Yeah, I know.
- [Sighs]
[Snaps fingers]
Focus.
You need another witness,
and at this point,
everybody else
in the firm is booked up.
Aw!
Is mommy helping you
clean up your mess, Ross?
Am I mommy
in this scenario?
What? Uh...
[Sighs]
Ross is just...
A baby.
So, okay...
Oh, my God.
I cannot believe
I'm gonna lose
to that tool.
Okay, come on.
No pity parties.
Go to an outside source
for the other witness.
For the best friend
you need somebody pretty,
sympathetic,
and most importantly,
willing to go above
and beyond for you.
[Pounding on door]
What are you
doing here?
Jenny, come on,
I need your help.
Got nowhere else to go.
[Door bolts
clicking open]
You yelled at me.
Kissed me.
Pushed me away.
Disappeared.
I haven't talked
to you in forever.
I don't even know
what's going on in your life.
Well, if you let me in,
I'll explain,
and I promise
it's a really good story.
So you've been living a lie
this whole time.
Uh...
Yeah.
That's awesome.
- Really?
- Yeah!
I mean, as far
as double lives go,
you're maybe not as cool
as Clark Kent, but still.
- Clark Kent?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, you're cut off.
- Mm.
Thank you.
What?
Nothing.
It just feels really good
to tell you.
I don't really have anybody
I can talk to about it.
You trust me.
Yeah.
I guess I do.
I like that.
Ooh, but I really like this.
[Chuckles]
[R&B music]
♪ ♪
[Elevator clicks]
[Door clicks open]
Mm.
Gotta hand it
to you, Harvey.
You may not be able
to commit to a woman,
but you have been
in this place
a very long time.
- She gets me.
- And has no needs.
I don't think you understand
how high maintenance
this place is.
He agreed
to all your terms...
Despite my protest
that he could do better.
- So we're done.
- Minus a few signatures.
- That's not done.
- Want me to leave?
[R&B music]
♪ ♪
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury, please note--
Can I ask a question?
No, you can't ask questions
as a witness.
Don't ask questions.
Ladies and gentlemen, please--
- yeah, okay, I know that.
But, um,
what are you doing?
- What do you mean?
- You're walking around
like you have
a giant stick up your ass.
[Scoffs]
It's a trial, Jenny.
I have to be powerful.
- But that's not you.
- Thanks.
No, you are charming,
and funny,
and trustworthy.
That's your power.
And that's great
when I'm trying to con my way
into the LSATs,
but this is a courtroom.
It's useless there.
But it's still you.
[Sighs]
So?
Take a deep breath.
[Inhales]
- [Inhales deeply, exhales]
- Okay.
Just talk to me.
Ask me
where do I work.
[Sighs,
clears throat]
Where do you work?
Lunders Global Initiative.
Ask me
how I know Sydney.
How do you know Sydney?
She was my friend.
And I've missed her every day
that she's been gone.
And why aren't you
friends anymore?
I don't know.
If you do it
like that...
They'll fall in love
with you.
[Upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Would you take this off?
Take it off.
- [Laughs]
- Take it...
[Speaks indistinctly]
[Laughter]
♪ ♪
Scottie,
that was amazing.
[Clicks tongue]
Careful, Harvey.
You need to hydrate.
You just ran
a marathon.
[Chuckles]
[Glass bangs on table]
And I think you
just beat me.
Uh-oh.
That's a lawyer look.
Law school.
Post-mock trial
in the library.
2nd Circuit Court
of Appeals.
Class action
on the prep room table.
Dempsey settlement,
in my office,
on the desk and under.
So what are we doing?
Um, a highlight reel?
As a matter of fact, we are.
Those were top moments, right?
- They weren't bad.
- No, they were great.
And I just realized
this was better.
You were the best
you've ever been,
and I know why.
Why?
You hid something from me
in the negotiation,
and I wanna know what.
[Laughs]
You know what?
You are ridiculous.
Oh, you know what?
Don't do that, okay?
- Do what?
- You think I don't know
victory sex when I see it, huh?
See it?
- What is it?
- [Scoffs]
Was it one of
Vega's properties is bankrupt?
The Buenos Aires one?
Wh-wh-what do you
want me to say, Harvey?
Yes, you got me!
I screwed you.
- How?
- Oh, my God.
You want
an anatomy lesson now?
That's my shirt.
Consider it
a winner's reward.
[Door slams shut]
Hey, Harvey.
You were right.
There's been a steady stream
of stock buying
by Vega's company
in the last 24 hours.
It's a hostile takeover.
Yeah, but why are they
disguising it as a merger?
They wanted access
to our private books.
- She tricked me.
- What?
She pretended she didn't
wanna hand over their books
so I wouldn't notice
when she asked for ours.
It's a classic maneuver.
She made me think
it was my idea.
How do you know that?
'Cause I taught her
how to do it.
So now they see how strong
Debeque's company is,
and they wanna buy it.
And they'll be running it
by the time Scottie's
back in London.
Wow. I leave you alone
for two days...
Yeah,
this is my mistake.
This is Halley's Comet.
Take a good look,
'cause it won't
happen again.
So what are you
gonna do?
I wanna know which
of Debeque's hotels
are the most valuable
and how fast
we can get them
on the market.
Wait, you want Debeque
to sell his best hotels?
It's called
the Crown Jewel defense.
We unload
the highest grossing assets,
and we make ourselves
look undesirable.
Debeque'll
never agree to that.
Trust me.
Debeque has enough passion
for his company that he'll
be willing to chop off an arm
to save the body.
Okay.
You know you had
that memorized
the first time
you read it, right?
Yeah, but I
didn't finish reading it
because a certain witness
chose to be distracting.
[Gasps] That must've
been rough for you.
Yeah,
you have no idea.
Mm. Where can I
get some water?
I need to make sure
my voice holds up.
Right there.
I'll make you a deal.
The winner gets the girl.
You know, I'm never gonna make
another deal with you again.
- No? Why not?
- Hey.
- Aren't you late for...
- Oh, I am.
They remind me of a younger,
less attractive you and me.
Please don't
say things like that.
And I know
that you rigged the lottery
so that Mike
would get Kyle.
Please. Rigged, expedited,
they're all just words.
Besides, don't you wanna see
what your boy is made of?
You talking bet?
Well, at least
three's a number.
- Yeah.
- Usual amount.
I believe
we have a wager.
Well, you know what?
Some of us shower
before we go to work.
[Clears throat]
Mr. Specter--
- You know what? Save it.
Right.
How you feeling?
- Good.
- Good?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Is it inappropriate
to take a Xanax
if you're a witness
in a trial?
I've seen clients
do much worse.
[Chuckles]
Actually, I'm not a client.
I'm a witness
in a friend's mock trial.
One thing--
if you get into trouble,
don't play the case.
Play the man.
What are you
talking about?
Good lawyers
worry about facts.
Great lawyers worry
about their opponents.
Kyle is cocky
and devious.
Figure out a way
to use that against him.
Okay.
Anything else?
Kick his ass.
- Who's your friend?
- Oh, uh, Mike Ross.
Do you know him?
Uh, yeah.
Uh, it's a big firm,
but I know who he is.
Yeah.
God, I don't know
why I'm so nervous.
I just know this
is a big deal to him,
and I don't wanna
let him down.
Hmm.
Sydney Thompson was at a party
and made a joke.
It wasn't meant
to be mean
or to be taken
as fact,
and it most certainly
was never meant to be public.
The defense will show--
that Sydney Thompson chose
to publicly defame her boss
with an impression
that she knew
would be damaging,
both to Lena Lunders' reputation
and her company.
I call Lena Lunders
to the stand.
[Sobbing]
Uh...Do you need
a minute?
No.
[Sniffles]
I can continue.
Thank you.
Please.
I'm a self-made woman.
I created
the global initiative
to target problems
in third-world countries.
I take my work
very seriously,
and if a joke
can be made of that,
fine.
But as a woman in power,
people look at your success
and label you.
They don't know
the complexity it takes
for a woman to succeed
in this business.
And when someone
undermines that,
well...
We have to fight
for ourselves...
Don't we,
Your Honor?
Objection.
So it's hard to be
a woman in business?
That has nothing to do
with the facts of this case.
Well, we can only understand
the damage your client has done
by fully understanding
the care with which Miss Lunders
has built her reputation.
Um, I'm sorry.
Can you ask me the question
one more time?
Take a deep breath.
[Sighs]
It's just you and me.
We're just gonna have
a conversation about your job,
okay?
Yeah, okay.
How do you know
the defendant Sydney Thompson?
We were coworkers.
We started at the same level,
and then I was promoted
to be her immediate superior.
And do you know
about the video in question?
Yes. I was at
the party that night.
And what were you
celebrating that night?
My promotion.
Same night.
That's interesting.
Miss Ginnesse.
What did you think
of the impersonation?
It was too far.
It was mean.
So why do you think
Miss Thompson did it?
Miss Lunders promoted me.
Sydney hated it.
And that's why
she made the video.
Well, thank you,
Miss Ginnesse.
Nothing further,
Your Honor.
Did Sydney ever tell you
that she hated
your promotion?
- Not exactly.
- Yes or no, please.
- No.
- Well, then how do you know
that she hated
your promotion?
I could just tell.
Can you tell what
I'm thinking right now?
That you're wishing
I would agree
with everything you say?
No. I was thinking
that if you could
actually read my mind,
I wouldn't bother
asking you the questions.
But you can't read my mind,
can you?
No, I'm--I'm
managing director--
No. And I'm pretty sure
you can't read Sydney's either.
And you actually have no idea
why she made that video.
Correct?
I guess I don't. No.
Good afternoon,
Miss Scott.
Thank you.
[Sighs]
Are you here to give me
a proper send-off?
I don't think we can do that
out here on the street.
- You sure?
- You tricked me.
I'm impressed.
To be fair,
Vega did want a merger.
I just convinced him that,
given your client's propensity
for rash purchases,
that allowing him to
stay in charge was a bad idea.
Vega needed Debeque's hotels
minus Debeque,
and I found a way.
One that he never
asked for or wanted,
and one that
he's never gonna get.
[Laughs]
Was--is this for real?
Three of Debeque's properties.
It'll be on the market
by the end of day.
He's never gonna let you
sell off
his crown jewels.
See, that's the thing
about passionate clients.
When they're crossed,
they get angry,
and they'll do anything
to get back.
Don't do this, Harvey.
Look, there's another way
we can do this.
We can get our clients
into a room together,
you can tell them
you were wrong,
and we can convince them
back into a merger.
Miss Thompson,
what was the intent
behind
your impersonation?
I was just trying
to be funny.
Everyone in our office
makes jokes,
and as a matter of fact,
Ms. Lunders encourages us
to be informal.
I can't win this
just on facts.
- ...Passed over for promotion.
- But I expected it.
I think everyone
has the impulse to move up,
but at a certain point,
you just have to let it go.
So that's what I did.
What are you gonna do?
I've never held
ill will for my boss.
I'm gonna play the woman,
not the case.
You say you expected
to be passed over
for a promotion, correct?
Yes.
And yet you applied
three times?
- Yes.
- And you were never promoted?
As I said, yes.
And when Nora Ginnesse
was promoted,
you wrote scathing emails
to the rest
of your coworkers in response.
No, not scathing.
The intent
was to be funny.
Oh, right,
you like to be funny.
Who doesn't like
to laugh?
Someone whose reputation
has been ruined.
- Objection.
- Just a thought.
- It's testifying.
- Sustained.
Mr. Ross, questions.
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
Forgive me. I was just
trying to be funny.
On your performance review,
Lena Lunders wrote,
"Good work ethic.
Lacks skills."
Do you think
that's a fair assessment?
Fair?
I--I don't know.
Well, your coworkers
were promoted,
and your boss
was calling you mediocre.
- Are you mediocre?
- No.
So why haven't you
been promoted?
I don't know.
Do you think
you deserve better?
- Doesn't everyone?
- So why haven't you tried?
- I have tried.
- Why haven't you improved?
I didn't say
I haven't improved.
Well, your review did.
Your five years
without a promotion did.
Look, you were so angry
that you weren't moving forward
that you lashed out
at your boss--
- No.
- Objection! Testifying!
- Everyone was moving past you.
- So what?
- People making good on their--
- Badgering, Your Honor.
- Sustained.
- People who could cut it.
I can cut it!
Excuse me,
Your Honor.
Settlement's
still on the table.
- What?
- Let's settle. Same deal.
Win-win.
- No, I'm good.
- Excuse me?
I've seen
the moony looks, Ross.
You like her, so you're
offering me a settlement
because you don't want
to hurt her feelings.
But I'd rather see
if you'll break her.
Giddy-up, cowboy.
Counselor.
Would you like
to proceed?
[Sighs]
No, Your Honor.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, Your Honor.
Nothing further.
Well, normally we'd move on
to closing statements,
but it's been a long week,
and honestly,
we all know
where this is going.
So court rules in favor
of the defendant.
[Bystanders applaud]
This court is adjourned.
[Gavel bangs]
Mr. Ross.
Naive and soft.
Not qualities we're looking for
at Pearson Hardman.
Gentlemen, I appreciate you
leaving the swords at home.
What started off
as a true merger
never needed to become
anything different.
Daniel, I want you
to listen to me.
I know Harvey, and he just
wants to merge your businesses
so he can double
his billable hours.
Quiet, Scott.
I wanna hear what he has to say.
I'm just here to get my client
the deal that he wants,
and what he wants is a merger,
is that right, Jones?
- That's right.
- Daniel.
Your law firm overreached
in a situation
where it wasn't necessary.
It's not entirely
Scottie's fault.
We lawyers all have
an instinct to win,
but sometimes we may not fully
understand what that means.
We understand
what it means.
Well, maybe you do,
and maybe you don't.
For me, it would be
to see both men
return
to the initial deal
so that you can grow
both your businesses,
instead of having one company
with a hostile reputation
and the other a shell
of what it once was.
I mean, that doesn't sound
like a win to me.
I'm sorry.
Let's just go back
to the original deal.
We can run it
together.
[Distant siren wailing]
[Knock at door]
You need anything?
'Cause otherwise
I'm gonna head out.
Celebratory drinks
with the associates?
Yep.
And what exactly
are you celebrating?
You know what? You can save
the disappointment, Harvey.
I know what I did.
Do you?
Because what I saw
is that you backed off
because you were
worried about hurting
your girlfriend's feelings.
It was a fake trial.
All right? I weighed
the pros and the cons,
and I decided it wasn't worth
hurting someone for the result.
The result is you just told
every partner in this firm,
including myself,
that you have a weak stomach,
that you don't have
what it takes.
You know, you keep telling me
that I have to decide
what kind of lawyer
I wanna be.
And if I were smart,
I'd probably be just like you,
because everybody
knows you're the best.
But I'm also trying to decide
what kind of person I wanna be.
And sometimes I like
my kind of person
a lot more than yours.
You wanna know
what kind of person I am?
Tough but fair.
I call it
like I see it.
And what I see is a kid
who asked for an opportunity
who still hasn't decided
if he wants it or not.
[Distant siren wailing]
[R&B music]
♪ ♪
Single malt, pleasel.
Harvard Club? I thought
you hate this place.
Vega kicked me out
of his hotel,
so, you know,
beggars...
[Sighs]
Save the pout.
You were head
of Law Review,
you clerked
for a Supreme Court Judge,
and you almost beat me.
I think that
deserves a drink.
On you.
I'd laugh,
but I just got fired.
From the firm?
No.
But the firm's
not going to be happy,
and that's why
I'm not already on a plane.
Hey, the Scottie I know
is tougher than that.
Is she?
Well, you wanna go back
to our Alma Mater
and see a lecture on why
women are better at science?
- [Laughs]
- Might cheer you up.
Maybe, but I'm
not going with you.
Come on,
we're still friends, aren't we?
I'm getting married,
Harvey.
His name is Steve,
and, uh,
he asked me a month ago,
and, um,
when I get back
to London I'm--
I'm going to say yes.
What would you
like me to say?
Nothing.
[Sniffles]
All right.
Come here.
I'm sorry I won.
No, Harvey...
I would hate it
if you were sorry about that.
[Energetic dance music]
♪ ♪
[Sighs]
You didn't have
to do that, you know.
- I know.
- I could've handled it.
- That was a thank-you,
if you couldn't tell.
I could tell.
So, um, Jenny
was a great witness.
Really likeable
and pretty.
Yeah.
Yeah, she is.
I know I was hard
on you this week.
- It's okay--
- No, it--
did you ever
take a minute to wonder
why I was
so mad at you?
I just expect more from you
than most people.
Why?
[Chuckles]
You're a smart guy.
You can figure it out.
[Departing footsteps]
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net