Are you watching me?
Do I look dashing?
Nobody says dashing.
James Bond says dashing.
You think you're James Bond?
I could be James Bond.
I've got Connery's swagger...
Definitely
Daniel Craig's physique...
Lazenby's...
I have no idea
what he's known for.
You okay?
I had an interesting
conversation
with Louis last night.
He said I should be careful
of you and Rachel.
Do I have anything
to worry about?
No.
He hates me,
and he's just trying
to get to me through you.
So you never--
No.
You got nothing
to worry about.
She's just a friend.
- Okay.
- And I'm late.
I'll call.
- Okay.
We should go out.
Uh, this is going out.
No, I mean you and me
and Rachel
should go on a double date.
Does she have a-a boyfriend?
I, uh, don't know.
No.
Going on a double date
with somebody from work
might be kind of weird.
If I get to know her,
then I won't worry.
- [Sighs]
- It'll be fun.
Just a couple friends
going out.
Right?
Awesome.
[Horns blaring]
Cab?
Someone steal your bike?
I have a lot on my mind.
It's a safety issue.
What are you talking about?
Louis told Jenny
about Rachel and me.
It was one kiss,
and she kissed me.
Okay, Soap Opera,
just give me my documents.
Harvey.
Cameron.
How the hell are you?
- Good to see you.
- Wow.
Too damn long.
Cameron Dennis,
district attorney,
meet Mike Ross,
my associate.
Hi.
I guess that makes you
his Harvey.
- I'm sorry?
- Harvey was my associate.
I taught him everything
he knows.
Best A.D.A. to come up
since me.
- You taught him?
- "Never go to court."
That's me.
"It's not about caring.
It's about winning."
Me.
No way.
Harvey's Harvey.
[Laughing]
Yeah, exactly.
We should, uh,
catch up, have lunch.
Hey, you know what?
This is crazy.
I'm free for dinner tonight.
Just cancel whatever you have,
and tell Jessica I demanded
that you clear your schedule.
Dinner it is.
It'd be nice.
That's my boy.
All right, you know where
to find me, 8:00.
Glad I ran into you, Harvey.
Ross, you still work here?
Funny.
Yeah, 'cause I thought
after I beat you--
Yeah, I got it.
- Thanks for expediting.
- Yeah.
Hi.
Do you need something?
Did you know that Harvey,
uh, was a prosecutor?
- No, he wasn't.
- Yeah, he was.
I've read every bio
at the firm.
People work
for the D.A.'s office,
it's on their bio.
Well, we ran into
Cameron Dennis this morning.
- The D.A.?
- Yeah.
He says that Harvey's
the best A.D.A. he's ever had.
No. Come here.
See? Nothing about being
a prosecutor.
Yeah.
I need you to go
on a double date
with me and Jenny.
Yeah, not gonna happen.
You have to.
Listen to me.
Louis warned her
about you and me.
Wha--
how did even get--
You know how.
'Cause he walked in
right after you kissed me.
If you say no,
she's gonna think
something's going on
between us.
Okay.
I'll go.
- Thank you.
- Freakin' Louis.
Oh, is this Harvey?
Okay, you are definitely
sending me that photo.
Westlaw lists him
as prosecutor of record
on pages and pages
of cases.
- Told you.
- I don't get it.
Why wouldn't he have this
on his bio?
Because.
Maybe he has something
to hide.
♪ Suits 1x11 ♪
Rules of the Game
Original Air Date on September 1, 2011
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ all right ♪
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
It touches some idealistic
core of your being,
where even the greatest cynic
has not given up hope.
That's why we listen
to music.
Oh, that's beautiful, Louis.
Really.
And I think your decision
to leave law
to become
a music critic
is in everyone's
best interests.
Okay, I was quoting
Peter Sellers.
I just got $1,000-a-head tickets
to Nixon in China.
Are you two dating now?
Should I come back?
Sit down, Harvey.
Love it when you talk to me
like my third grade teacher,
Mrs. Coe.
Gentlemen.
Malcolm Price died last week.
Truly great loss
for humanity.
You want to mock the dead?
Fine.
But his tabloid,
Nothing But the Truth,
has made us a fortune.
Price has left his estate,
ten companies,
including the tabloid,
to his two daughters,
Madison and Kelsey.
We have been asked
to divide the assets up fairly.
And I'm here why?
Because they hate
each other.
Malcolm structured the will
to bring them back together.
You have a knack
for bringing parties together
who don't see eye to eye.
So why is he here?
Because Madison Price
requested him.
You sure she's not mixing him
up with me?
Hardman had me do
some contract work for her
a couple years back,
so I guess I made
an impression.
Right.
So you each get a sister.
You think pitting us
against each other
is fair to Louis' client?
Please.
Dividing financial assets?
- You couldn't shine my shoes.
- Someone should.
Well, actually,
I personally shine my own shoes,
so there you go.
- Oh, lucky them.
- How come you always ask Donna,
"Donna, by the way,
those are really nice shoes
that Louis has on"?
Gentlemen.
We're on the same side.
And although I would not choose
to have you both on this,
that is how it fell.
So I expect you to put
your differences aside
and work together on this
so that everyone
can be happy.
Can you manage that
this time?
She's always hated me.
Maybe this is a chance
to put all that behind you.
I'd like that.
Really, I would.
But Maddie?
I don't think so.
Maybe she'll surprise you.
Kelsey's a bitch.
She doesn't deserve
any of it.
Well, I'm afraid your father
didn't share
that point of view.
According to his will,
we were meant...
To find a division
of these companies
that makes both of you happy.
But I want to make sure...
That you're happy.
You want to know
what will make me happy?
Whatever makes her miserable.
It's simple.
I want Nothing But the Truth.
My father and I worked together
on it for years, and...
It made me crazy.
The two of them pretending
that tabloid was literature.
It means everything to me.
All I want...
Is to sell off
that piece of garbage
and for her to get
as little as possible.
What made her
so mad at you?
She blames me for our dad
leaving her mother
and marrying mine.
How can she think
that's your fault?
Because her mother
got pregnant
and used it to rope in
my dad.
And then little Kelsey became
the center of his universe.
You know what it's like
to have someone hate you
out of pure jealousy?
We'll get you the paper.
Do you know what it's like
to watch someone else
get all the attention
when you know that you're twice
the person they are?
She's not getting that paper.
[Phones ringing]
- Maddie.
- Kelsey.
- Louis.
- Harvey.
Doctor, doctor.
- Chevy.
- Nice.
Good meeting?
Yeah, we connected.
You?
We're on the same page.
Hm. What was, uh,
Kelsey looking for?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask Jenny?
You seem to like talking
to her.
[Keyboard clicking]
No, Mike,
that's not distracting.
I was just waiting.
For what?
To not be distracting.
How come Harvey doesn't talk
about working
for the D.A.'s office?
- Who told you that?
- Cameron Dennis.
We ran into him
this morning.
They're having dinner.
So that's why he wouldn't tell
me where he was going.
What's going on, Donna?
Let it go.
Don't ask Harvey about this.
What's the big secret?
It's no secret.
Just...
Don't.
And what are we talking about?
The Price sisters.
Those girls.
Mm.
Do we really have to play nice
with Louis?
I wanna crush him.
You wanna crush him?
Get over to the paper,
kick the tires,
and figure out what it's worth.
I thought we were supposed
to use
the independent valuations.
What, you think he's gonna
play by the rules?
I know he won't.
That's why you better be three
steps ahead of him,
because I can guarantee you
Louis'll be two steps
ahead of you.
Speak of the devil,
her majesty's here
to see you.
- I heard that.
- You were meant to.
- Gentlemen.
- Your highness.
Okay, you know what?
That's exactly why I'm here.
To be mocked?
No, to set clear ground rules,
to keep the negotiation
above board.
Absolutely.
No kicking, no biting,
and no rabbit punches.
And now you're mocking
the ground rules.
No, I'm just mocking you.
Point one.
We both agree to use
the independent valuations.
Absolutely.
Good point.
Point two.
You do not call Jessica in
to mediate.
This is you and me.
You afraid mom's gonna take
my side?
No, I know mom's gonna take
your side.
- Because I'd be right.
- Point three.
Chinese wall.
You can't access any internal
documents that I create.
Let's make Jessica proud.
We do this right,
everyone walks away happy.
Wonderful.
Don't worry.
We'll still crush him.
- I heard that.
- You were meant to.
Care to make a wager?
Our job is to make
both sisters happy.
How do we know who wins?
Both: We'll know.
- Usual amount?
- No.
I think we should change it up
this time.
I win, I get Mike.
You can't bet me
like I'm chattel, Louis.
It's not like
he's gonna win.
- One month.
- Ten days.
- Harvey.
- Two weeks.
- Nine days.
- Harvey!
All right, you know what?
Fine. Ten days.
And in return?
Well, that's tough
because anything you have
I wouldn't want.
What? Uh, you're gonna bet me
for nothing?
Harvey?
Harvey Specter.
Alexandra Leeds.
I hear you're working
for the Attorney General's
office.
And you're fighting
for the oppressive capitalists.
Winning
Oh, good for you.
We should have lunch.
Catch up.
Who told you
I was coming here tonight?
No one.
I haven't seen you
in five years.
You wanna catch up?
You want something
from me,
and it isn't lunch.
I want to talk
about Cameron Dennis.
Six feet, Pisces, wavy hair.
I'm serious.
I haven't worked for Cameron
in over a decade.
What's there to talk about?
The Attorney General
is investigating allegations
that he systematically
buried evidence
to get convictions.
So talk to people
who actually work with the guy.
No, that's the problem.
He's still their boss.
Nobody's talking.
Neither am I.
Over lunch
or anywhere else.
So best of luck.
Harvey.
I was hoping
for some lunch.
I'm having you subpoenaed
to testify
before a grand jury.
Enjoy your dinner.
Give Cameron my best.
Hey, Harvey.
Glad you could make it.
How are you?
Tell me about
the bullshit run-in
that you staged this morning.
How long did you have to wait
so that you could pretend
to be surprised to see me?
Ten minutes.
You're never early,
but I didn't want to cut it
too close.
I also just had
another little run-in
with Alexandra Leeds.
You really want
to drag me into this?
Calm down, Harvey.
I'm not dragging you
into anything.
They're dragging me
into this.
It's election year nonsense,
and I wanted to warn you.
So you asked me here
to warn me?
Yeah, and to reassure myself
that you've got my back.
How bad is it?
It's nothing
I can't handle,
but I'm glad you're here.
Look, Harvey.
Whatever differences we had,
we were a good team.
The truth is that...
if anything taints
the work that we did,
it'll be bad
for both of us.
Is that a threat?
Not at all.
It's just reality.
We put away bad people, Harvey.
We fought tough battles,
and we won.
I taught you how to win.
That's not exactly
what you taught me.
I know that you didn't
always approve
of the means,
but we both know
that the end result
was always right.
You're still the best
smooth-talker I know.
Use it now.
Talk your way out of this.
Settle.
'Cause if this goes to court,
there are skeletons
to be found.
They won't find them.
You wanna bank on that?
I have your back.
I am not volunteering anything.
But if push comes to shove,
I won't perjure myself.
Not even for you.
[Smooth blues music]
♪ ♪
How was dinner
with the antichrist?
Subpoena came for you.
What are you gonna do?
What would you do?
I'm sorry.
Are you feeling okay?
You just asked my advice.
All these years--
yeah, I think that's a first.
You were there.
What would you do?
I'd tell them everything.
I'd watch Cameron go down.
I'd throw a party.
I'd drink champagne.
I'd go to bed,
and I'd sleep like a baby
after I did it.
Really?
Don't equivocate.
He's poison, Harvey.
Leaving there was huge.
You could've gone
down a dark road.
And I'm telling you,
I would not have followed.
I just got back
from the paper.
Nice place.
It's a growing asset.
There's opportunity
for expansion.
If we get this thing
for Kelsey,
I think she's set.
I saw Elvis there.
Great.
Exciting.
Am I interrupting something,
or...?
Dinner didn't go well?
It was okay.
Old times.
If that's how
you want to play it.
Let's talk about this proposal
for Louis.
You know what?
Why don't you take
a run at it?
Get the best deal you can.
You bet me, and now you're
hanging me out to dry?
That's fine.
I'll do it.
And I'll win.
Oh, did you decide
what you want him to pay you
when I win?
His tickets
to Nixon in China.
You want to go to the opera.
No, but Louis does,
and making him miss it
would be amusing.
So you get nothing.
You are betting me
for nothing.
- Are you still talking?
- Right.
So did you find a date
for tonight?
Yep.
And?
And we'll see you there.
What?
I thought that's what
you said you wanted.
To sit with you and Jenny
and have her seeing
into my brain
the whole time?
Seeing what?
You do remember
that we kissed, right?
I remember.
It'll be okay.
Hi.
Uh, is this a good time
to talk
about division of assets?
No.
Is there a better time?
Yes.
When Harvey's available.
Harvey asked me
to handle it.
He thinks you can beat me?
Prove him wrong.
What's there to lose?
Ex--except for Nixon in China,
of course.
What do you have for me?
Okay, so there are
ten companies.
We propose that Kelsey takes
companies one, three,
seven, and nine.
So that gives us...
52.3% of the assets.
Hm, generous, but no.
Uh, alternatively,
we propose that Kelsey takes
companies one, two,
four, and eight.
That gives you--
54.6%.
No.
Do you have
a counterproposal, or--
No.
Okay, uh, Kelsey takes
companies one, seven,
eight, and nine.
No.
Louis, that gives you 60%
of the assets.
Yes.
But no.
What is it
your client wants?
Well, your offer
makes it infinitely clear
what your client wants.
The tabloid.
And what my client wants
is for your client
to not get what she wants,
so you can't have
the tabloid, period.
You're legally required
to take these offers
to your client.
So bring me up
on ethics charges.
Or report me
to your supervisor.
Oh, wait, shit.
I am your supervisor.
Hold on one second.
Go ahead.
What are your complaints?
Have any? No? Really?
We're supposed to find
a fair and equitable settlement,
Louis.
Okay, you go run
and tell Jessica.
Oh, wait, that would be
breaking the rules,
and then you've have to come
work for me.
So why don't you run along now
and get Harvey
and tell him
to get off his ass
and join the negotiations.
Because you just failed.
When you left
the D.A.'s office,
you said you were done,
you had learned enough,
and that you were ready
to move on.
Was that just bullshit?
You were the one who wanted me
to have trial experience.
You said that Cameron
was the only one
that I should learn from.
And what exactly
did he teach you?
Harvey, why did you leave?
He had a case.
I caught him burying
a key piece of evidence
he was obligated
to turn over.
The guy was guilty.
The defense would've used it
to let him walk.
All right, what kind
of exposure do you have?
I told him no,
but he didn't listen.
Then you were obligated
to report him.
Which is why I left.
Why didn't you tell me this
at the time?
Because you put me there,
Jessica,
to be mentored.
Okay? And it occurred to me,
that might've been exactly
what you wanted me to learn.
For the record,
it wasn't.
I'm gonna represent you
at this deposition.
I'm gonna try to keep you
from talking.
But I think you should.
He was my mentor.
He is a public servant.
The standards are higher.
He was my mentor.
And I am not gonna be
the one to expose him,
any more than I'd ever turn
on you.
Worst dating story--
identical twins.
I was a lab rat
for their social experiment.
They were trying to prove
that women were shallow
and can't see
beyond the surface.
And they wanted to get laid.
Yes, that too.
Good times.
So you slept with them both.
Almost.
Turns out they weren't identical
after all.
Wow.
Excuse me, I am just going
to run to the ladies' room.
Oh, I'll go with you.
Okay.
What's wrong, Mikey?
Tough day at the office?
Didn't see you.
It could've been worse.
That's good.
So you and Rachel.
How long have you guys
been dating?
You know how lawyers
and clients work close
over the course of a trial.
When we kicked your ass
in the mock trial,
we, uh, bonded.
You know
in the real world
dating clients is a violation
of ethics, right?
Good thing it's not
the real world.
'Cause I intend to violate
those ethics
all night.
You know the funny thing?
I always thought
you'd get there first.
I'll tell you how she is.
Shut up, Kyle.
Someone might think
you're jealous.
you're a dick.
Oh, wait.
Somebody already does.
That's good.
You should write that one down.
Do you keep a journal
of these things?
Finish your tofu.
So how did you two meet?
Um...
I dated his best friend.
I know, it's awful.
But he was a bad guy,
and I didn't see it.
Mike showed me.
The truth is, I--
I think there was always
something there with us.
But nothing happened until
Trevor and I were totally done.
Never?
Well, we did kiss once.
Hey, having fun?
Loads.
Right, Mike?
I think we're gonna go.
What? No.
We're having fun.
Come on, you don't want
to ruin this.
- Yeah.
- Kyle, really, just--
okay, Kyle, just--
What? What's the problem?
Stop it.
She doesn't like it.
God, that guy is such a tool.
So what?
He's not your date.
Yeah, well,
I have to work with him.
That's not why
it bothers you.
He's with Rachel,
and you know it.
Oh, my God, Jenny.
We have been over this.
I've seen the way
you look at her.
I've seen it before.
It's the way
you used to look at me
when I was with Trevor.
Jenny--
I'm going home, Mike.
Decide what you want.
In or out.
I like you.
A lot.
But you can't have both.
I worked as an assistant
district attorney
for the county of New York
for two years.
Tell me about your
relationship
with Cameron Dennis.
Vague.
Did you and district attorney
Cameron Dennis
work closely together?
He was my boss.
He supervised all my cases.
And were you personally close?
- Subjective.
- A judge would allow it.
And yet there's
not one here.
Do you really think
by deposing him on the stand
you're going to intimidate him?
I think deposing him here
will let him know
what it will be like
if this evidence
is brought forward at trial.
You're not getting
to trial.
If your client doesn't
perjure himself right now,
I won't have to.
Were you and Cameron Dennis
close personally?
He was my mentor.
It's a hard relationship
to define.
Moving on, counselor.
All right.
We don't have to talk
about Mr. Dennis.
Let's talk about you,
Mr. Specter.
In two years,
you handled 18,362 cases.
36 cases a day.
That's beyond impressive.
Thank you.
You took 147 to trial,
winning them all.
Don't go to trial
if you're not gonna win.
Why'd you leave?
An attorney by the name
of Jessica Pearson
helped me get
through law school,
and she felt that I could use
trial experience.
But I always planned
on ending up at her firm
and paying her back
by earning that firm
outrageous settlements.
How am I doing?
You could do better.
You two think
that this is a joke.
Argumentative.
You're damn right
it's argumentative.
Because he knows
that laws have been broken,
and he has an obligation
to report it.
Ms. Leeds--
But if this is the way
you want to play it,
the Attorney General
has given me
a broad mandate to uncover
what went on.
And it need not be limited
to Mr. Dennis.
Were you part of the problem,
Mr. Specter?
Vague.
I'll rephrase.
In your capacity
as assistant district attorney
in the county of New York,
did you knowingly
suppress evidence
in violation
of the A.V.A. Rules of Conduct,
the N.D.A.A. Standards,
and the New York State Bar
Rule 8.4, section c?
My client would like
to exercise
his fifth amendment rights
at this time.
I hear you botched
a settlement
by negotiating against yourself.
I didn't--
You let Louis know
the one thing
that was most important
to our client.
Okay, yes,
I made a mistake.
But Louis made one too.
Well, he didn't mention that.
Yes, he knows
what our client wants,
but now we know the one thing
his client wants.
She doesn't care
about winning, Harvey.
She just wants our client
to lose.
Okay, well, that's good.
So what's next?
We lose.
We give her the tabloid.
Well, how does that make
our client happy?
We let Madison have
the paper,
and then we take
everyone who works there,
and we start a new one.
They all love Kelsey.
Nothing But the Truth
is just a name.
We let Madison have it.
I have taught you
a thing or two.
Well, I see that you're
up to speed.
Well, as am I.
Um, I noticed that there were
some employee issues
at the tabloid.
You know,
contracts about to expire.
So I just want
to let you guys know
that I went ahead and locked up
all the key employees.
Just to protect us.
Since we're all working on this
together, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Good.
- He knows.
- He can't.
- He does.
- I was careful.
I deleted every file
from the server.
The only time any paper trail
left my locked desk
is when I faxed it
to Kelsey.
Oh, you faxed it.
From the large machine
that stores all the information
you put in it
to be printed back later
by anyone who has your code?
He can't do that.
We have a Chinese wall thingy.
Oh, God, he's gonna beat us,
isn't he?
Look, he knows what
we're up to,
but he couldn't keep his tactics
to himself.
So we can use that
against him.
And that's how
we'll crush Louis.
Refresher course, Harvey.
You and Louis
aren't opponents on this one.
You're working together.
Like Captain & Tennille?
Well, if so, he's Tennille.
Who?
You need to come with me.
What, am I in trouble?
Yeah, Harvey.
You are.
Gonna buy me a drink
before you screw me?
Sit down, Harvey.
Listen to what she has
to say.
You got me trembling
in my boots.
You're a small fish,
and you don't even swim
in the pond anymore.
But if I have to eat you alive
to get to Cameron Dennis,
I will.
This is my case against him.
Falsifying DNA tests,
coerced confessions,
testimony buried.
You have all this.
Why do you need me?
Because this is circumstantial.
You have the crimes,
but you can't physically tie
them to Cameron.
He's a dirty public servant,
and I think
it's why you left.
Your record was too good
to just walk away.
Maybe I got greedy.
- Harvey.
- I'm not testifying.
You're being stubborn.
And this isn't one
where you get to make
the call.
I'm sorry.
I've done all I can.
It wasn't just his cases
he cheated on.
Hector Avila.
Take a look.
You think you were really
that great?
You think your
great track record
was because of your skill?
I got two theories here, Harvey.
Either you're wasting your time
protecting a man
who screwed you
from the beginning,
or you didn't just know
he did this.
You participated.
In which case
I'll have you disbarred.
Come on.
Damn it.
What are you doing?
Uh, nothing.
I'm just sending
some faxes.
Stand down.
They're stuck, Donna.
What are you gonna do?
[Whispering]
I'm the fax whisperer.
Okay, that's ridiculous,
all right?
I've tried everything.
I've hit--
I've already done that.
And it didn't--
whatever.
United International
wants to buy the tabloid?
Uh, whatever you do,
don't say anything to Louis.
Kelsey Price
does not want to sell.
Not a word.
Thanks.
Whoa.
Something explode in here?
Just doing some research.
Yeah, 'cause you always do
your own research.
Okay, closed-door meeting
with Donna,
with Jessica.
Dinner with some D.A. you've
never even mentioned before.
Is this all something
Cameron Dennis taught you?
Keep secrets from everyone
because you're so good,
you don't need
anyone's help?
There's an investigation
into evidence tampering.
I've been asked to testify
against my old boss...
or face charges myself.
You could be disbarred.
If I'm found guilty.
Are you guilty?
Not of evidence tampering.
I would never do that.
Of anything else?
Anything I ever did,
you put me in front
of an unbiased judge,
I walk away clean.
You put me in a courtroom
with a grand jury,
anything can happen.
So are you gonna testify?
I'm not sure
what choice I have.
Well, some dickhead
once told me
that when they put a gun
to your head,
it's not just give in
or be killed.
There are 146 other options.
You'll figure something out.
[Knock at door]
I'll have a proposal for you
in the morning,
and I think
we'll all be happy.
All right?
Night.
He took the bait?
Like shooting a fish
in a barrel.
Good work.
Where you going?
I just might take
your advice.
The tides are turning.
You turning with them,
Harvey?
They turn you?
Hector Avila.
You don't even know,
do you?
Is this some old case?
It's my old case,
and you buried evidence.
You wearing a wire,
Harvey?
No, you're not.
I can tell.
I'm not that easy to read
anymore, Cameron.
You are to me.
Hector Avila.
Was he guilty,
whoever he was?
- He was my case.
- Guilty is guilty.
That's not the way
the system works.
The system is broken,
and you know it.
It's not reasonable doubt.
Juries want to be sure
without a shadow of a doubt.
It was my case.
You worked for me.
They were all my cases.
You're a disappointment.
No.
You're the disappointment.
You could've been D.A. yourself.
You are twice the lawyer
than any of the pricks lined up
to run against me.
But you sold out.
You help rich people
keep their money.
That's all you do.
I stack my value to society
against yours,
and I win by a mile.
So you're selling me out?
We both know they don't want
to put you in jail.
That's not what this
is about.
Walk away, Cameron.
Make a deal.
Let someone else be D.A.,
and all of this,
it goes away.
Otherwise?
You know what happens
if you talk.
They start reopening cases.
Maybe Hector Avila
walks away.
He murdered once.
He'll murder again.
You do remember him
don't you?
Oh, I remember 'em all.
Maxwell Rankin?
What was it, uh,
34 or 35 women that he raped?
Alberto Plank?
You remember him?
He burned his children alive.
You'll open the floodgates,
Harvey.
Do you want that
on your conscience?
Then make a deal.
It's on you
to keep them in jail.
Okay.
Okay, Harvey.
You win.
This isn't winning.
Good to see you, Harvey.
Let's do it again soon.
So your client's really
willing to give Madison
Nothing But the Truth?
You made it clear
it was non-negotiable.
I convinced my client
to settle.
She wants to move on.
You're sure
there isn't anything
that you want to, uh,
disclose?
Nope.
I think we're good.
Then we're good.
Everybody's happy.
Mm-hmm.
As clams.
Thank you, Louis.
You, um...
Happy with the deal?
Yeah, as a matter of fact,
I am.
You?
[Chuckles]
You don't even know
the half of it.
Don't I?
Are you happy that your client
got the paper
or that you turned around
and sold it?
Oh, you didn't think I knew
about that, did you?
Want to know why
I'm happy, Louis?
I'm happy because when you read
over that offer
from United International,
I wanted you to read that.
I wanted you to sell
to them.
Because the thing
you didn't know
is that yesterday Kelsey Price
bought United International.
You shouldn't go
behind people's backs, Louis.
You shouldn't try
and access information
that's none of your business.
It could backfire.
Mm.
I think we need to talk
to Harvey.
I'm sorry, Harvey.
You set me up.
No, Louis.
You set yourself up.
The sales offer
was meaningless
until you read it.
This is cheating.
You cheated, Louis.
You broke the rules,
and you have to pay the price.
People may think that lawyers
will do anything,
that they can do anything.
Now, I'm not willing
to accept that, okay?
You can't go skirting
the rules
and justify it
because you think someone else
broke the rules, okay?
You cheated!
And you lost!
End of story.
Harvey, I won.
His play acting
by the fax machine
was so obvious.
I found out Kelsey owned
United International,
and I thought if they wanted
the paper so badly,
how much would they overpay
for it?
50%.
Harvey, you overpaid 50%
for a business
so buried in expenses
from the employee deals
that I made,
it can barely stay afloat.
And then all I had to do
was convince Madison
to sit back, have fun,
watch her sister fail miserably.
I won.
Your client got
what she wanted.
So did ours.
Jessica asked to make
everyone happy.
Everyone's happy.
It's a draw.
Just hold on a second.
You tell me the truth
right now.
Is this a win to you?
Fine, Louis.
You win.
You were a step ahead.
You got Mike.
Ten days.
You think I'd want him now?
I just wiped the floor
with him.
You can keep him.
How can I help you?
I'm not gonna let him
take the fall
for that asshole.
Have a seat.
Harvey didn't see it
for a long time.
I mean, Cameron's good
when he wants to be.
You know how I judge
a man's character?
Not by how he treats
his equals,
but by how he treats
the underlings.
Lowest rungs on the ladder.
You always impressed me
in that regard.
Thank you.
Harvey would never use this,
and he'd kill me
if he knew I had it.
But can you help him?
Can you use this
to help him?
Is Harvey punishing you
for something?
Louis.
No! You lost?
You have to work for him?
I lost, and then he said
he didn't want me.
He farmed me out.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Is there anything I can do
to help?
What?
That.
What are you talking about?
I wanted you for months.
Rachel, I flirted.
I-I-I made up some scheme
where we were married.
And you made it clear
you don't date anyone
from the office.
Until I start seeing
someone else.
Okay, you're delusional.
Why did you bring Kyle
on that date?
Because it was last-minute
and because you needed me
to help convince your girlfriend
that you don't like me.
You did it to get to me.
This is crazy.
It's just stupid.
You don't even like
the guy, Rachel.
Jenny comes to drop off a suit
at the office,
and what do you do?
You kiss me.
You know, I seem to recall
you kissing me too.
Yeah, that's the problem.
I did.
And it was great.
But it's too late.
You were too late.
And I can't do any of this.
- Do what?
- This, this.
This you joking
about your first time or--
or rubbing my shoulders
or--or touching my arm.
You're playing with me,
and you know it.
What I know is
you're playing with me too.
You kept flirting with me
long after you started
dating her.
Yeah, well,
that's gonna stop.
Good.
You know,
and while you're at it,
no more running to me
for favors
or asking me for help.
How 'bout you find yourself
some other paralegal?
Because as far as I'm concerned,
we're done.
[Indistinct chatter]
Uh, can you give us
a minute?
Well, Jessica.
I've spoken
to Alexandra Leeds.
She told me
about the deal you cut.
What do you want me
to say?
Hmm.
This is a copy.
I'm driving over
to the Attorney General's office
right now.
If she doesn't tell me
you've cut a new deal
by the time I get there,
she gets the original.
And then I give her
the proof.
You don't have the proof.
Don't I?
Cut a new deal.
And if you ever mess
with one of mine again,
Alexandra gets that anyway.
You don't have to testify.
They don't need you anymore.
Cameron made a deal?
He made a deal
to sell you out.
But I made my own deal.
He'll be stepping down,
spending some quality time
with his family.
How exactly
did you manage that?
Not your concern.
But you're
in the clear, Harvey.
Some people would be happy
with that news.
That son of a bitch.
Clifford Danner was 18.
I put him in jail
12 years ago.
Kid's been rotting in prison
his whole adult life.
And?
He's innocent.
Cameron buried the evidence.
If I'd had it...
Do you have enough
to overturn?
I don't know.
So what are you going to do?
I'm gonna get him out.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net