[Horns honking]
[The Constellations'
Perfect Day]
♪ ♪
♪ it's a perfect day ♪
♪ to go and tie one on ♪
The 2011 Tesla Roadster Sport,
offered only to our most
exclusive members.
You know your vehicles.
I promise to have her back
before she turns into a Pontiac.
- Hey, Harvey.
- Laurence.
How would you feel
about taking something
other than the Tesla tonight?
- It goes against my policy.
- What policy?
My "I want the Tesla" policy.
- Yeah.
- Tell you what.
You know more
about the car than I do,
it's yours.
Horsepower.
Really?
That's where we're starting?
Well, if it's so simple,
just answer it.
288. Top speed.
125 miles an hour.
0 to 60--
3.7 seconds.
Yeah.
You know your cars.
I'm an enthusiast.
And I've been waiting
for the Tesla for months.
Okay.
Laurence.
Knock yourself out.
So why'd you let him have it?
Because it never hurts
to have a man
who runs a $2 billion
hedge fund owe you one.
But if you're
just gonna give it to him,
why bother to compete first?
Because if I didn't beat him,
he wouldn't feel
he owed me one.
I'm suddenly
feeling old school.
Why don't you surprise me, huh?
♪ ♪
[Engine revs]
Are you Mike Ross?
Harvey told me to tell you
that 8:00 means 8:00.
♪ It's a perfect day
to waste away ♪
♪ your perfect plot to play ♪
♪ just another perfect day ♪
♪ but before you know
it's gone ♪
Glad you showed up.
Oh, hey.
I'm sorry. I was just--
Shut up.
Listen.
You see these cars?
Yeah. They're awesome.
They suck.
They're nothing
compared to this.
Whoa.
The engine in this car
is made by McKernon Motors,
the industry standard
in formula one.
In fact, they've won
more championships
than any other engine
on the planet.
How do you know all this?
Avery McKernon
was the first client
I ever brought into the firm.
- Was?
- He died three months ago.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry--
Not the point.
McKernon's engines
and his company
have something in common--
They win, like me.
And because I win, I've been
promoted to senior partner,
which means you'll be handling
all their paperwork.
Oh, so you brought me here
to give me an appreciation
for the product.
No, I brought you here
to meet Robert Stensland,
the new CEO.
He'll want to put
your name with a face.
How do you know?
Because Robert's a tightwad,
and we don't bill you out
for nothing.
Wait a minute.
Is this conversation
right now billable?
You bet your ass it is.
Yes. Up top. Come on.
What? We're making
all this money.
We can't celebrate it?
Not in poor taste.
Dominic. Mike, I'd like
you to meet Dominic Barone,
the man responsible
for the design and production
of this engine.
This is my new associate,
Mike Ross.
He's just a kid.
Are you trying to steal his soul
before he hits puberty?
Okay, obviously...
You're still upset
about our labor negotiations.
My-- My workers
took a big hit.
And McKernon took a bigger one.
Both of which poised the company
to be strong for years.
I was always
straight with you about that.
Sophisticated words
for a guy who screwed us.
Look, I'm sorry
you feel that way,
but you have to admit,
I did have the courtesy
to do it from the front.
Wow. Yeah,
he really appreciates
what you've done
for the company.
Robert Stensland,
I'd like you to meet
your new associate, Mike Ross.
We're not paying him
what we pay you.
Nor should you, but I assure
you he's highly effective.
Well, I'll believe it
when I see it.
I had him read
your corporate lease last week.
Ask him anything.
That's a 300-page document.
Okay, what are the terms?
Okay, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
The named lessee
was the parent company,
Glendon Enterprises.
35,000 square feet
at 19 west 57th.
$80 a foot.
Expires in six months
with an option to extend.
Exercisable in 30 days.
- Who signed the lease?
- You did.
- What's my middle name?
- The letter "L."
What happens in the event
the company no longer exists?
That wasn't in the lease.
How can you be sure?
Because the lease
I read wasn't 300 pages.
It was 364.
And I can tell you what's on
any one of those pages,
but I can't tell you that.
That's how I can be sure.
Excellent.
You can get him started
on the new deal right away.
- New deal?
- Yeah.
I have found a buyer
willing to spend $200 million
for the ground underneath
the flagship factory.
Where are you moving
manufacturing?
Well, that's the beauty of it.
The real asset of
McKernon Motors is the name.
We move overseas,
we save ourselves a bundle.
Up front payout
while retaining the name
and maintaining
cash flow over time.
That's genius.
Exactly.
All right,
we'll take care of everything.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Thanks.
- Really?
Jesus.
I knew he was cheap.
I didn't realize
he was an idiot.
What are you talking about?
The asset's not the name.
It's the quality.
He moves overseas,
it's gonna kill the goose
that laid
the goddamn golden engine.
Wait a minute.
I thought you didn't get
emotionally attached
to the client.
I'm emotionally attached to me.
Look, I made a bet
that this company would grow
and my billables
would grow with it.
We're holding a pair of aces,
and this asshole's
trying to fold.
So?
What are you gonna do?
I'm not gonna do anything.
You're gonna
go through those bylaws,
and you're gonna find me a way
to get rid of Robert Stensland.
No, no, no, no.
I have to go see my grandmother.
Uh-uh.
- Is she dying?
No.
Cancel on her.
[Rock music]
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
[Cell phone rings]
[Rings]
Uh...
Ugh.
Yeah.
Did you find anything
that'll help me
get rid of Stensland?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
Well, if you're not here
when I need it,
what good does that do me?
What? It's 7:15...
[Stammers]
[Door opens, closes]
Did you get it?
Picked it up yesterday.
Did you sleep with it
under your pillow?
How I sleep
is none of your concern.
Yeah, neither
is the Yankees' batting order,
but that doesn't stop me
from thinking about it.
Harvey.
Promise me you won't be cocky.
I understand
what's at stake here.
I'll be perfectly humble.
Great.
You ready?
You kidding?
I was born for this.
7:45.
Nice of you to show up.
Uh, yeah, I was up
till 5:00 in the morning.
I'm kidding.
But Louis Litt wants to see you,
and I don't kid about that.
- What does he want?
- I don't know.
Louis doesn't let me in
on his game plan,
but I kind of
prefer it that way.
Okay, um, can you tell him
that I have to see Harvey first?
Your call.
But, uh, if you're gonna be
sleeping in your suits,
you may want to keep
a fresh one in the office.
Is it that bad?
It's worse.
[Exhales] Come on.
I'd just like to say
this is an honor,
I take it seriously,
and I intend
to make you all proud.
Except you, Fred.
I gave up on making
you proud in '99.
Okay. There is one more
order of business.
He's not here.
No.
Where is he?
He's at his senior partner
initiation.
Oh. That's great.
But let me ask you something.
What's the difference
between a senior partner
and...Other partners?
Isn't that something
you should have been studying
when you were pretending
to go to Harvard?
Okay. Senior partners,
they buy into the firm.
They share in the profits,
but they also
have to put up equity.
So how much does it cost
to buy in?
$1/2 million...
Right now?
Harvey, you knew
what the buy-in was.
You knew today was initiation.
How could you not
have the money?
I didn't think
it was due today.
It's not due today, is it?
No. It's not.
[Laughter]
Every man in this room
fell for exactly the same thing.
Does that include you?
No.
No, it doesn't.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Peanuts, gluten, strawberries.
What is this?
A shopping list?
No, it's just a list of foods
that I'm allergic to,
so when you select the venue,
these foods
are not to be on the menu.
A venue for what?
No one told you?
- No one told me.
- Oh, drats.
Well, a long-standing
Pearson Hardman tradition
is the rookie dinner,
which means you, the...
- Rookie. Yes.
- That's right.
Are to host a dinner
for your fellow associates.
Well, come on.
Don't look so blue.
Oh, it's okay.
It's really easy.
All you have to do
is just find a unique location
and then coordinate
with 50 other associates.
It's really simple.
No pressure.
And you're allergic to chicken?
No, I just don't like it.
Oh, by the way,
what was so important
that you had to see Harvey
before you came to see me?
Louis,
Harvey doesn't really--
Can we-- Can we-- Can we--
Can we just-- Shut up.
Okay.
Let me just get something
straight, okay?
When I ask you a question,
I just expect an answer.
Uh...
McKernon Motors.
I was working
on the due diligence.
And why would that require you
to look at the bylaws?
State law requires
a summary be prepared
in the event of a sale.
Privately held corporations
are exempted.
Not if the sale
exceeds 150 million.
According to who?
[Typing]
[Computer beeps]
The state's website.
I like to be thorough.
Well, put it there, buddy.
Are you fricking serious?
[Mutters]
I understand Stensland
is throwing a large amount
of legal work our way with the
McKernon Motors factory sale.
How'd you know that?
I hear things.
You taking care of him?
I am.
By the way, for when it is due.
What's this?
It's a cashier's check
for $500,000.
[Laughs]
You had this the whole time.
I've had the money since I
set my sights on senior partner.
Nice of you to finally make it.
Why does everybody
keep saying that?
Because you're
supposed to be here
when you're supposed
to be here.
Doesn't seem to apply to you.
I'm not the topic
of this conversation.
Now what'd you find me
on McKernon Motors?
The board can't vote
for at least 24 hours
after the CEO presents a deal
involving the sale
of company land.
But Stensland already
presented it to the board.
Right, but Stensland isn't CEO.
I wrote those bylaws myself.
He's CEO.
Hmm.
Page 238, clause 137
states if the CEO dies,
an interim CEO
will be appointed
until the board
convenes an election vote,
which can't be called
till the next fiscal quarter,
in this case next Thursday.
So they can't vote him in
until Thursday?
Thursday.
Okay.
Well, prepare the due diligence
for me to take to Stensland,
but I don't want anything
ready to sign.
- Where are you going?
- Out.
I have until Thursday
to find a new CEO.
- Huh.
- What?
Oh, nothing.
Uh, you know, just six hours,
1,500 pages, and I, uh,
I found your mistake.
Yeah, you found
the one mistake I made
while drafting those bylaws
a dozen years ago
when I was two years
younger than you.
A mistake, by the way,
that's gonna help me
get rid of Stensland.
Mistake.
Excuse me, Mr. Specter?
I was wondering if you might
need a hand sometime
with one of your matters.
Uh, any one.
Well, Allen--
It's Aaron.
I think that says it all,
don't you?
What are you doing?
Uh, I'm looking
for a restaurant.
Where did you go
for your rookie dinner?
I came into the league
a sophomore.
You better not be
prioritizing that
over McKernon Motors.
I still need something
to stall Stensland.
It's right here.
What are you
so irritated about?
I spent a day
with a top headhunter I know
who couldn't produce one
legitimate CEO candidate
by Thursday.
What about
that Dominic Barone guy
who runs production?
You said he was responsible
for the engines,
and he clearly cares
about the workers.
No, he's not the guy.
Oh, you're scared
you can't convince him
because he hates you.
I get it.
Nice try.
You know you can't
host your dinner there.
That's a Wachtell, Lipton,
Klein restaurant.
Okay. Fine.
What about this place?
Yeah, that'd be great
if it was 2004.
[Sighs] Oh, my God.
Why does any of this matter?
God.
You see that guy
over there by the fax?
Take a good look.
He's never gonna make partner.
Okay. Let me guess.
Because he threw
a lousy rookie dinner?
No, because he doesn't get it.
Get what?
He doesn't get that doing
good work isn't the whole job.
Part of getting it
is that things like the dinner
actually matter,
even when
you don't think they do.
Look,
you were giving me shit
this morning because
I come and go when I want to.
You know why I can do that?
Because when I got here,
I dominated.
They thought I worked
100 hours a day.
Now, no matter
what time I get in,
nobody questions my ability
to get the job done.
Get it through your head.
First impressions last.
You start
behind the eight ball,
you'll never get in front.
- Hey, you busy?
- It's 7:00.
I'm not here
'cause I like the view.
And don't misunderstand me.
When I say "the view,"
I'm referring to your face.
That's funny,
because I'm hideous.
- What's up?
- You're a foodie, right?
Why do you say that?
Because you're the only person
I've ever seen order
a shrimp, red pepper,
and goat cheese pizza.
Well, right,
but without the pepper,
what connects the goat cheese
and the shrimp?
I'm a foodie.
Okay, so I need your help
finding a restaurant
for the rookie dinner.
Well, that's unfortunate,
but I'm swamped,
and I don't have time
to teach you about cuisine.
Well, no,
don't make me remind you
that you owe me one.
How's that?
You told Louis I was working
on Harvey's case before his.
Because you told me to.
Well, now I'm telling you
to help me with my dinner.
Mm.
- You-- Okay.
- Good luck with that.
Not gonna help me
with my dinner.
Now I'm talking to myself.
Yeah, grammy.
[Knock at door]
No, I told you I was coming.
I'm-- I'm on my way, okay?
Yeah.
Um, 15 minutes.
Okay. Bye.
Hey, what are you--
Okay, what was that for?
If you cared about me,
you would have told me
what Trevor was up to
a long time ago.
I was trying to protect you.
How is hiding the fact
that my boyfriend
is selling weed protecting me?
You want to know the truth?
Your boyfriend also happens
to be my best friend, all right?
I didn't feel
like ratting him out.
If you were really his friend,
you wouldn't just stand by
and let him throw his life away.
Let him? Let--
I've never let Trevor
do anything. Have you met him?
Trevor listens to you,
and he needs you right now.
Oh, my God.
He is throwing his life away,
and you ditched us.
Both.
Like we didn't mean
anything to you.
I'm...I'm late.
Louis.
What are you doing here?
Hi.
Uh, Stensland called.
And apparently the diligence
wasn't proceeding apace.
He called you?
Yeah, he called me,
I called him,
what's the difference?
The paperwork
was taking too long,
and I got it done.
I suggest you stay
the hell away from my client.
Harvey.
Glad you could make it.
We were about
to sign the papers.
I got word back at the office.
I just came to see how Louis
was getting around the bylaws.
I...Don't know.
Ah...
I'm at somewhat of a loss.
Robert, I'm sorry.
This is what was holding up
your due diligence.
Technically,
you're still interim CEO
until the board
votes you in on Thursday.
If protocol isn't followed,
it leaves you with huge
litigation exposure.
That's right.
Well, I imagine
we should hold off, then.
Please don't blame Louis.
It's my fault.
We usually have senior partners
oversee transactions like this
because junior partners,
they tend to miss things.
See you Thursday?
One second.
Uh, just so you know,
you were a junior partner
until recently.
There's a reason
I'm not anymore.
Okay. Take it easy.
So what if you took a trip
to Russia with another man?
I mean, that was before
you met grandpa Jimmy, right?
He didn't care
it was before I met him.
Never shut up about it.
So what was
this other guy's name?
Gregory mind your own business.
Ooh.
So, Michael, this has been fun.
Now why don't you stop
beating around the bush
and tell me what's going on.
Trevor.
It's Trevor.
It's always Trevor.
He's gotten himself
into some really bad...
Stuff, and I think he needs
my help to get out of it,
but I've been under
so much pressure,
and I know you've always told
me to be there for people...
No, no, listen to me.
Screw Trevor.
What?
You're moving forward,
and he'll do whatever he can
to keep you where you are.
Yeah, but...
But no buts.
That kid is an anchor.
You need to cut him loose.
- Whoa.
- You owe me 50 bucks.
What's going on
with Robert Stensland?
What did Louis tell you?
You're not dealing with Louis.
You're dealing with me.
What are you hiding?
Nothing.
I looked through the bylaws
and precluded
potential litigation.
You looked at the bylaws
for a tactical reason,
and I want to know what it is.
I want him out.
That is not your call.
You are an attorney.
This is the internal business
of McKernon Motors.
Look, McKernon had a plan,
and I didn't spend
a decade shaping it
to let this fool throw it away.
McKernon is dead.
So what?
Doesn't mean the plan's no good.
You fail, we'll get fired.
He moves overseas,
our billables ll be gone
in five years, anyway.
Better five years than nothing.
You know what?
That's Stensland's attitude,
and it's a losing one.
Harvey, I don't think
you have any business
telling that man
how to run his company,
but I know you don't
have any business
telling me how to run mine.
You are a senior partner.
You are not
a gunslinger anymore.
Back off Stensland
and close the deal.
I need you to prepare
the draft CEO candidate speech
for Thursday.
Well, I thought you
were supposed to back off.
Yeah, I'm supposed to do
a lot of things.
I'll call you with the plan
on my way back.
From where?
From convincing
the man who hates me
to do what I say.
Oh, right.
You mean the guy I suggested
you go to in the first place.
Do you remember that whole
getting it thing
I was talking to you about?
What, I can't even gloat?
Gloating's fine.
You just have to not suck at it.
Okay.
Thank you. So much.
That hurt.
Hey, Ross.
You left your search
for the rookie dinner
on your computer.
Why don't you just save time
and take us to Friday's?
Ooh, ooh, somebody's mad.
Devon, looking at my computer
is a violation of exactly seven
hostile workplace
environment statutes.
What are you gonna do?
Sue me?
No.
No, no, no.
I'm just gonna use it
as legal cover
if I decide to kick your ass.
Dominic.
Harvey,
what are you doing here?
Our contract's good
for two more years.
I need a word.
In private.
Excuse me, bill.
Make it fast,
'cause this is a place
where people actually
work for a living.
Well, keep in mind
people are watching.
Just try to keep
your expression neutral.
You know, they don't teach
deceptive tactics
where I come from.
Then you're gonna learn
under fire.
Stensland's shutting you down.
What? Why?
For money.
He's got a buyer for the land
under the factory.
Why are you coming to me?
Because the only way
to stop him
is for you
to challenge him as CEO.
What?
Are you crazy?
You've got a management title.
That I choose
not to identify with.
You run the factory.
Which I never left,
'cause I have no taste
for boardroom politics.
You've been here since day one.
You know the product
inside out.
These workers,
they respect you.
Pew, that's a lot of smoke.
How many people
did you go to before me?
- Seven.
- Right.
I never said
you were my prom queen.
Look, I want to win, okay?
I went to those other people
because they were better
suited to get past the board,
not better suited for the job.
Those are the facts
whether you like it or not.
And why should I trust you?
Because if you don't,
there aren't any jobs
left to negotiate over.
You and the factory,
you're finished.
[Cell phone chimes]
What are you working on?
Um, nothing.
Just some stuff for Harvey. Why?
Wrap it up.
Louis Litt wants to see you.
This time
he doesn't want to wait.
Furthermore,
I feel that with
the proper strategic
and synergistic alliances
moving forward--
I have to actually believe
what you're saying.
They're just platitudes
that don't mean anything.
Yes, they do.
Synergistic alliances
mean you form relationships
to get the cost down
and your product out.
It's never gonna work.
Well, it better goddamn work.
My ass is on the line.
What about my ass?
If it wasn't attached
to your thick head,
maybe we wouldn't be
having this problem.
I'm sorry I'm not
as well practiced
at corporate double speak
as you'd like,
but I've been busting my ass
on this for two hours.
So if you're not happy
with my progress,
then why don't you
get the hell out?
He doesn't leave
without getting it.
[Door closes]
Son of a bitch.
You're not gonna pick it up?
Why should I?
Never gonna get it.
You're right.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What's your engine design
philosophy?
Perfectly balanced
power and durability.
Okay. Why don't you favor
power like Bronson does?
Because drivers are limited
to eight engines a season,
and Bronson's don't last.
Well, so you would
stack your engines
up against Bronson's, then?
Uh, I have stacked
my engines up against Bronson
and everyone else's
in the world,
and mine win.
Why?
Because I make sure
they're designed better
than anyone else's in the world
from the day
that they're conceived
to the day they're born.
And that's why people buy them.
Goddamn right.
And that's the speech
you're gonna give.
[Clears throat]
Good lawyer, bad lawyer, baby.
Worked like a charm.
Come on.
You know you want it.
There it is.
Told you.
Someone doesn't like you,
you use it against them.
Or, in this case, for them.
I didn't do this for Dominic.
I did it
to get rid of Stensland.
Wow. Have you ever considered
writing for hallmark?
Many times. Yeah.
Congrats.
Looking good.
Hey.
I said don't be late.
Late? I'm not late.
When you host your dinner here,
not being late means getting
here a half hour early.
Aha. So what made you
change your mind?
The food items are samples
to help you select your menu,
so since I could never really
afford to eat here myself...
Mm.
Okay, start there.
- Try that?
- Yes.
It looks kind of funny.
So does an egg roll.
I don't accept that premise.
You want my help or not?
Ugh. What is that?
Squid.
I-- I think
it's still moving.
That's what I'm talking about.
Mm.
I don't get it.
How do you have no appreciation
for fine food?
Mm. We didn't have a lot
of money growing up.
I don't know.
I guess I'm just comfortable
with what I'm comfortable with.
That is the exact
opposite of me.
I've-- I've always
loved new experiences.
And your parents?
They're loaded.
Mm. So then what do you need
a free meal for?
I want to live on what I make.
Mm.
- What?
- Nothing.
I was just thinking about
Dominic for a second.
And then I realized
this is the first time in weeks
that I haven't been
thinking about work.
That's what new
experiences do for you.
Being a foodie doesn't mean
only liking fancy food.
Means having
the courage to try it.
And then you get to serve
what you like.
Except strawberries, peanuts,
gluten, and chicken.
Okay, why not those things?
Because Louis is an asshole.
If you can't serve things
just 'cause Louis is an asshole,
you're not gonna have
that many choices.
Good point.
[Cell phone ringing]
So what really
made you change your mind?
Pity.
I'll take it.
[Laughs]
Driver, taketh me
to Williamsburg.
[Beep] It's Jenny.
Trevor told me
you talked to him,
and he's gonna stop.
Thanks, Mike.
Hold on.
Change of destination.
Trevor.
What are you doing here?
Can we talk for a minute?
Yeah.
I know you lied to Jenny
about us talking.
You never should have told her
I was dealing
in the first place.
I never should have had
to hide it in the first place.
[Sighs]
Look, Trevor, you don't need
to be dealing for a living, man.
You could make something
of yourself.
Is that what
you came here to tell me?
You've got real
software clients, man.
Stick to them.
Jeez.
You believe that crap?
I don't have
any software clients.
Jesus.
You're as naive as Jenny.
Look...
If you need some kind of
transition money or something--
What? How?
Does it matter?
Look, what matters is that
you don't help me out, okay?
I help you out.
And I'm not interested
in transitioning into anything.
Okay.
But the least you could do
is be honest with Jenny.
That's what this is all about.
- Yeah.
- You always liked her.
I think she deserves
to know the truth.
You always thought
you were better than me.
[Scoffs]
Maybe that's because I am.
[Both grunting]
Come on now.
All right?
[Coughs]
We're done.
Don't let the door hit you--
[Sighs]
Call Dominic?
He's waiting for us outside.
He's got the speech down?
Yeah, he's got it down.
Better.
I'm taking a big risk on him.
You're taking a risk on him?
Look at him.
He's scared out of his mind.
He's leaving his comfort zone
because you convinced him to.
So?
So maybe some words
of encouragement.
The best way to help Dominic
is not to let him
second guess himself.
The most important asset
an attorney has
is his ability
to always be self-assured.
Okay.
Here's what's gonna happen.
It's standard for me
to prep the board
on any voting procedure.
When do I speak?
When I tell you to.
Let's go.
I suggested to Stensland
you be there
to convince the board
the production won't be hurt
by an overseas move.
It helps your credibility
that he brought you here,
and it'll hurt his when
you challenge him for CEO.
[Clears throat]
Look, it's natural
to be nervous, okay?
Just remember,
you know your stuff.
The board's never
loved Stensland,
and I'm here to back you up.
Okay.
Robert.
Harvey.
You know, I have to admit,
I almost didn't see it coming.
Excuse me?
It was the delay
in the due diligence.
It just didn't smell right.
So the only thing it could be
was that you were going after
my CEO appointment.
So since I'm still within my
rights to move a board meeting,
I did.
I was voted in today at noon.
And tomorrow the board will
ratify the sale of the factory.
And now I'm firing your firm.
And I'm firing you.
Try the croissant, gentlemen.
Marmalade's fantastic.
What are we gonna do?
You're gonna go through
those bylaws again,
and see if there isn't
another way
we can stop this sale.
I'm talking about Dominic.
He just lost his job.
He's a grown man.
He made a decision.
[Sighs]
Because you convinced him to.
Based on your idea,
which I recall
you pushed on me at the time.
Because I thought
it would work at the time.
Well, it didn't. What do you
want me to do about it?
Help him.
He's not dying.
He lost his job.
He has to look for another one.
Which, if he hadn't chosen
to fight for his company
in the first place,
would have happened anyway.
Now, show me that you get it,
go back through
those bylaws again,
and see if you missed anything.
Okay?
So this is what happens
when you promote the wrong guy
to senior partner.
If you hadn't gone
to Stensland behind my back,
this wouldn't have happened.
You don't know that.
And I'm a member of this firm
just as much of you.
Oh, I think we both agree
that you're a member.
For your information,
I didn't even--
Louis.
Harvey, eye on the ball.
The issue here is you tried
to torpedo a client--
The client is McKernon Motors,
not Stensland.
You didn't let me finish.
Without my consent.
That trumps
the "who's the client" part.
Louis, go to Stensland,
repair the relationship.
Say what you have to.
Call it a misunderstanding.
Promise Harvey
is no longer involved.
Consider it done.
Wait a second.
Louis didn't go to Stensland
behind my back.
You send him there
to hedge your bets.
Either stensland's out
and we double our billings,
or you have plausible
deniability,
and he stays with the firm.
Wow. Am I smart enough
to do that?
If I win, I look great.
If Louis wins, he looks great.
Either way...
You look great.
You mean the firm looks great.
Harvey, what I've been trying
to get into your head
is that you bought in.
You are the firm.
That's it.
Mike, follow me.
I need you
to go talk to Dominic.
What? Why?
Stensland's already CEO.
That won't matter
if we just buy the damn company.
What?
Why are you still working?
It's one of my creations.
I'm not leaving it unfinished.
What the hell do you want?
I'd be happy to tell you
if you put that wrench down.
Yeah, you're quick
with the jokes.
I'm the guy who just got fired.
[Sighs]
You're right. I'm sorry.
What would you say
if I told you
we could get your job back
and stick it to Stensland.
I'm done with Harvey
and his plans, yeah?
You were there.
We got fired too.
You and Harvey still have jobs?
He doesn't care
about anybody but himself,
including you, Mike.
Yeah.
You're probably right.
But he did stick his neck out
to keep your company here,
and he does have an idea
that requires your help,
so you can stay here
and call him an asshole,
or you can come with me
and we can help him.
Give me my goddamn shirt.
You know,
it goes from 0 to 60--
In the blink of an eye.
Did you bring me down here
to tell me I can drive this?
Better.
For $250 million,
you can own it.
McKernon Motors is for sale?
If we act fast.
I'll need
to see the financials.
You put together
a letter of intent,
they'll get you the financials.
You know, their real asset
is engine quality.
I don't want
to just buy the name.
Speak of the devil.
Laurence, I'd like you
to meet the man responsible
for every McKernon Motors
engine ever built.
Wow. Dominic Barone.
Very nice to meet you.
Good to meet you.
I'd like to show you something
if you have a minute.
Absolutely.
So how do we get an offer
to the board
before they vote to ratify
the deal tomorrow?
You're gonna
go through those bylaws,
and you're gonna
figure something out.
I don't have to look through
them to figure it out,
because I just did.
Well, what took you so long?
You trying to look like me?
Each of you have 24 hours
to review the documents
in front of you,
so at this time...
Uh, excuse me.
Excuse me.
What is he doing here?
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna take care of this.
No, no, I will.
You gentlemen have no right
to attend this meeting.
Actually, we do.
The bylaw states
that any original employee
has the right
to petition the board
any time they meet.
Dominic Barone
has assigned that right to me.
He was fired.
He no longer has that right.
Per section 17-5, point "C,"
Dominic wasn't given
three days' notice,
so technically he wasn't fired.
Which is why
I do have the right
to urge the board
to accept the offer
for the purchase
of McKernon Motors.
Now, I can tell you
that this offer
will keep manufacturing here
and save jobs
while retaining
the flagship engine
that put this company
on the map,
but I don't have to,
because it happens to be
for way more goddamn money
than the one
in front of you right now.
Hey, Bob.
How are ya?
It's funny
how you held out on me
on that proper
notice exception.
I didn't hold out.
I made that up on the spot.
Really? On the spot?
Remember that
getting it stuff--
I know, right?
I'm getting it.
Well, I was gonna say that,
but now you ruined it.
That's one thing
you definitely get.
How to ruin it.
How to ruin it?
I heard that.
[Clears throat]
I have to admit,
you don't suck.
I wish I could say
the same for you.
Time to pay the Piper.
Just so you know,
I took the liberty
of ordering some
really expensive wines.
Hope that's okay.
[Nervous laugh]
Sorry, sir, but the check's
been paid for in full
by a Harvey Specter.
There, uh, might have been
some gluten in the ravioli.
I hear McKernon Motors
is getting a new owner.
We're not only
handling the sale,
but with the expansion plan
they're putting in place,
our billables should double.
Nicely done.
I did it for the firm.
[Phone beeps]
[The Constellations'
Perfect Day]
♪ ♪
♪ it's a perfect day
to turn away and run ♪
What are you doing here?
You were right.
I should never
have kept it from you
that Trevor was dealing
all that time.
Well, I mean, it's, uh...
It's all in the past, right?
No.
What are you talking about?
He's lying to you.
He's still dealing.
And I'm done with him.
Son of a bitch.
Well, thank you, uh,
for telling me.
No, don't. Stop.
We're even.
And that is the last time
I am ever ratting on anyone.
So if you fall for it again...
It's on you.
Are you angry with me?
You told me
he would listen to me.
- I thought he would.
- Well, he didn't.
I...
I'm sorry.
I'm s-- I'm sorry.
No, I can't.
I can't.
What?
No, I-- I fought with him.
Oh, God.
This is too much.
Oh, my God.
[Cell phone ringing]
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net